ok so what's now first today we'll talk about training neural networks again and
확인 그래서 우리는 다시 신경망을 훈련에 대해 얘기하자 오늘은 이제 첫 무엇과
then I'll give you a bit of an interview coming to show that works before we dive
나는 우리가 다이빙을하기 전에 작동 쇼에 오는 당신에게 인터뷰의 비트를 줄 것이다
into that the material just some administrative things first first I
그 소재 단지 일부 관리 것을 먼저 첫 번째 I로
didn't get a chance to actually interviews Justin last lecture justin is
기회를하지 않았다 실제로 인터뷰 저스틴 마지막 강의 저스틴입니다하기
your instructor also for this class and he was missing for the first two weeks
이 클래스 또한 강사 그는 처음 2 주 동안 실종됐다
and they can can ask me anything about anything he's very knowledgeable maybe
그들은 그가 어쩌면 매우 지식의 나에게 아무것도에 대해 아무것도 요청할 수 있습니다
that's an understatement
즉, 삼가의
ok and the 72 is out as a reminder it's quite long so I encourage you to start
확인하고 72 그렇게 꽤 오랫동안의 알림 내가 시작하는 것이 좋습니다으로 밖으로
to build here and it's do basically next Friday so get started on that as soon as
여기에 구축하고는 기본적으로 다음 주 금요일은 그래서 가능한 한 빨리 그에 시작 할 수있어합니다
possible and you implement know that works with the proper API of forward
가능하면 앞으로의 적절한 API와 함께 작동 노하우를 구현
backward classes and you'll see the abstraction of a competition will grab
뒤로 클래스와 당신은 경쟁의 추상화 사로 잡고 볼 수 있습니다
and go back to my session drop out and then you'll actually implement
다시 내 세션으로 이동 중퇴하고 실제로 구현합니다
commercial networks so by the end of this assignment to actually have a
상업 네트워크 실제로이이 과제의 말 때문에
fairly good understanding of all the low-level details of how come on strong
강한에 오는 방법의 모든 낮은 수준의 세부 사항을 매우 잘 이해하고
network classifiers I'm just ok so where we are in this class just as a reminder
네트워크 분류 난 그냥 확인 해요 그래서 우리는 단지 신호로이 클래스에 위치
again we're training neural networks and turns out the training on networks is
다시 우리는 네트워크에서 훈련을한다 밖으로 신경망을 훈련하고 회전하는
really a four-step process you have an entire dataset images and labels we
정말 4 단계 프로세스는 전체 데이터 세트의 이미지와 라벨 우리가
sample a small back from the dataset we thought propagating through the network
우리가 네트워크를 통해 전파 생각했다 데이터 세트에서 작은 백을 샘플링
to get to the loss which is telling us how well we're currently classifying
우리는 현재 분류​​하고 얼마나 잘 우리에게 말하고있는 손실에 도착합니다
dispatch of data and we back propagates to complete the gradient of all the
데이터의 파견 그리고 우리는 모두의 기울기를 완료하기 위해 전파
weights and this gradient is telling us how we should not sure every single wait
무게와이 그라데이션이 우리에게 말하고 우리가 어떻게 매일 대기 확실하지해야
in the network so that we're better classifying these images and then once
네트워크에 우리는 더 나은 다음 번에이 이미지를 분류하고 있도록
we have the gradient we can use it for a primary update where we actually do that
우리가 실제로 그렇게 할 경우 우리는 그라데이션 우리가 차 업데이트를 사용할 수있다
small notch
작은 홈
last class we looked into activation functions and I'm tired of activation
지난 시간 우리는 활성화 기능으로 보면서 나는 활성화 피곤 해요
functions and some pros and cons of using any of these insider neural
기능과 어떤 장점과 이러한 내부자 신경 중 하나를 사용의 단점
network a good question came up in Piazza so when asked why would you even
물었을 때 좋은 질문이 너무 광장에서 들어오는 네트워크 이유도 당신 것
using your activation function why not just skip it and question was posed it
정품 인증 기능을 사용하는 이유는 그냥 건너 뛰고 질문을 제기했다하지
and I've got to really address this very nicely in the last lecture by basically
난 정말 기본적으로 마지막 강의에 매우 능숙하게이 문제를 해결하는 데있어
if you don't use an activation function than your entire neural network ends up
전체 신경망이 끝나는 경우보다 활성화 함수를 사용하지 않는다면
being one single in your sandwich and so your capacity is equal to that of just a
당신의 샌드위치 하나 하나가되는 등 용량 단지의 그것과 동일하다
linear classifier so those activation functions are really critical to have
그 활성화 기능이 정말 중요하다, 그래서 선형 분류
between and they they are the ones that give you all this way that you can use
사이에 그들은 그들은 당신에게 당신이 사용할 수있는 모든 방법을 제공 것들입니다
to actually put your data we talked briefly about the preprocessing
실제로 데이터를 넣어 우리는 전처리에 대해 간단히 이야기
techniques but very briefly we also looked at the activation functions and
기술하지만, 아주 간단히 우리는 또한 활성화 기능을 보았고,
their distributions throughout the neural network and so the problem here I
신경망 여기 그래서 문제 전반에 걸쳐 자신의 분포 I
see your call is we have to choose this initial weights and in particular the
우리는 이러한 초기 가중치를 선택해야하고 특히 전화가 참조
scale of how large you want those who wait to be in the beginning and we saw
기다리는 사람들을 방법을 큰 규모는 처음에하고 우리는 보았다
that if that if those weights are too small then your activation in a neural
이 경우 그 그 무게는 신경에​​ 활성화 너무 작은 경우
network as you have a deep network goes toward zero and if you set that skill is
네트워크는 깊은 네트워크가 0으로 이동이 있고 당신이 설정 한 경우 그 기술은 그대로
likely to higher than all of them will explode instead and so you end up with
그들 모두보다 높은에 가능성이 대신 폭발하고 그래서 당신은 끝낼
other super-saturated networks or you end up with networks that just about all
다른 네트워크 슈퍼 포화 또는 해당 단지에 대한 모든 네트워크와 끝까지
zeros and so that scale is very very tricky thing to set we looked into the
0과 1 그래서 그 규모는 우리가 들여다 설정하는 매우 매우 까다로운 일이다
initialisation which gives you a reasonable kind of thing to use in that
당신이에 사용하는 것은 합리적인 종류를 제공 초기화
form and that gives you basically roughly good active activations or
형성하고는 기본적으로 대략 좋은 활동 활성화 또는를 제공합니다
distributions of activation throughout the network in the beginning of training
훈련의 시작 부분에서 네트워크를 통해 활성화의 분포
and then we went into best normalization which is this thing that alleviate a lot
그리고, 우리는 많이 경감이 일에 가장 정상화에 들어갔다
of these headaches with actually setting that skill properly and Sebastian
실제로 제대로 그 기술을 설정하고 세바스찬 이러한 두통의
legislation makes this a much more robust choices they don't have to
법안이에게 그들이 필요 없어 훨씬 더 강력한 선택한다
precisely get that initial scale correct and we went to all of its present calls
정확하게 맞 초기 규모를 얻고 우리는 현재의 모든 호출에 갔다
and we talked about that for a while and then we talked about the learning
우리는 잠시 동안 그것에 대해 이야기하고 우리는 학습에 대해 이야기
process by trying to show you a kind of tips and tricks for how you actually be
당신이 실제로 할 방법에 대한 팁과 트릭의 종류를 표시하려고에 의해 처리
said these neural networks how you get them to train properly and also how you
말했다 당신이 그들을 어떻게 또한 제대로 훈련받을 방법이 신경망
run across violations and how you slowly over time in to get up rendering just so
위반에 걸쳐 실행 방법 천천히 시간이 지남에 너무 렌더링 일어나
we talked about all that last time so this time we're going to go into some of
우리는 몇 가지로 갈거야 그래서이 시간에 대한 모든 것을 지난 시간에 이야기
the remaining items for training neural networks in particular parameter up the
위 특정 매개 변수에 훈련 신경 네트워크의 나머지 항목
schemes I think most part and then we'll talk a bit about my l'ensemble dropout
계획은 나는 대부분의 부분을 생각하고 우리는 내 난 앙상블 드롭 아웃에 대해 조금 얘기하자
and so on so before I dive into that any administrative things my way that I'm
나는 그 어떤 행정 일에 난 내 길을 뛰어 등등 전에 있도록
forgetting not necessarily so
잊고 반드시 그렇게
primary updates because there's a process to training a neural network and
차 업데이트 신경망을 훈련에 프로세스가 거기에 있기 때문에
this is a pseudocode really in what it looks like that about you violate the
이것은 정말 당신이 위반에 대해는 그 모습에 의사입니다
law severely the gradient and performer primary update when I talk about
법에 심각한 그라데이션 내가 얘기 공연 차 업데이트
parameter updates were specifically looking at this last line in here where
매개 변수 업데이트는 특히 여기 어디에서이 마지막 줄보고 있었다
we are trying to make that more complex where so right now what we're doing in
우리가 만들려고하는보다 복잡한 그 어디 그래서 지금 우리가 무슨 일을하는지
school just reading the st. where we take that break into my computer and we
학교는 단지 일을 읽고. 우리는 내 컴퓨터 및 우리에 그 휴식을 취할 곳
just multiply it scaled by the learning rate on to our primary factor we can be
그냥 우리의 주요 요인의 학습 속도에 의해 확장 및 곱셈 우리는 할 수 있습니다
much more elaborate with how we
훨씬 더 정교한 방법으로 우리
on that date and so I flash this image briefly in the last few lectures where
해당 날짜 등등에 나는 지난 몇 강의 곳에서 간단히 이미지를 플래시
you can see different parameter update schemes and how quickly they actually
서로 다른 매개 변수를 업데이트 방식을 볼 수 있습니다 얼마나 빨리 그들은 실제로
optimize this simple loss function here and so in particular can see that STD
여기에 간단한 손실 함수를 최적화 그래서 특히 것을 볼 수 있습니다 STD
which is what we're using right now in the fourth line here that's a speedy and
우리가 여기에 네 번째 줄에 현재 사용하고 그 발 빠르게 그리고 무엇 인
read to you can see that that's actually the slowest one of all of them so
그 사실 때문에 그들 모두의 가장 느린 하나입니다 것을 볼 수 있습니다 당신에게 책을 읽어
practice you rarely ever use just basic custody and are better schemes that we
당신은 거의 이제까지 단지 기본 양육권을 사용하지 연습하고 더 나은 방식이다 것을 우리
can use we're going to go into those in the structure so let's look at what the
우리가 이제 무엇을 살펴 보자 구조에서 이들에 갈거야 사용할 수 있습니다
problem is with Sgt why is it so slow so consider this particular slightly
문제는 너무 느려 약간이 특정을 고려하는 이유 하사관 함께
contrived example here where we have a loss function surface level sets of our
우리는 손실 함수 액면 세트가 여기에 인위적 예 우리
loss as opposed to elevated long one direction much more than another
손실은 다른 것보다 훨씬 더 높은 긴 한 방향에 반대
direction so basically this loss function here is very shallow
여기 방향 때문에 기본적으로이 손실 함수는 매우 얕은입니다
horizontally but very steep vertically and we want to of course minimize this
수평으로하지만, 매우 수직으로 가파른 물론이을 최소화하기 위해 우리가 할
and right now we're at the Rex Baltimore trying to get to the minimum denoted by
우리가 렉스 볼티모어에있어 지금이 가리키는 최소려고
the smiley face that's where we're happy but think about what's the trajectory of
우리가 행복 만의 궤도 무엇에 대해 생각 어디 웃는 얼굴
this is both X&Y directions
이 모두 X 및 Y 방향이다
judy if we try to optimize this landscape with that look like so what
주디 우리가 같은 그 표정이 풍경을 최적화하려고하면 그래서 뭐
would it look like horizontally and vertically I see someone's butt so what
그것은 수평과 같이 수직으로 난 그렇게 누군가의 엉덩이를 볼 것입니다 무슨
are you planning out there and why is it so I'm going to bounce up and down like
당신은 거기 계획하는 이유는 그래서 최대 반송 가서 아래처럼 있어요된다
that and why is it not making a lot of progress right is basically has this
그 이유는 많은 진전를 잘 기본적으로이가되게하지 않습니다
forum where when we look at the gradient horizontally we see that the radiant is
우리가 그라데이션 볼 포럼 수평 우리는 복사가 있음을 볼 수
very small because this is a shallow function horizontally but we have a
이 수평 얕은 기능을하지만 우리가이 있기 때문에 매우 작은
large rating because it's a very steep function as to what's going to happen
큰 평가는 무슨 일이 일어날에 관해서는 매우 가파른 기능이기 때문에
when you roll out a street in these kinds of cases and you end up with this
당신은 이들 종류의 경우에서 거리를 출시하고이 끝낼 때
kind of pattern where you're going way too slow in horizontal direction but
당신이 수평 방향으로 너무 느린거야 패턴의 종류 만
you're going way too fast and vertical direction because you end up at this
이에 결국 때문에 당신은 너무 빠르고 수직 방향을거야
year so one way of remedying this kind of situation as we recall and momentum
올해 하나 이런 상황 또는 치료의 방법을 우리는 기억으로 모멘텀 그래서
update to the momentum update will change our update in the following way
기세 업데이트에 대한 업데이트는 다음과 같은 방법으로 우리의 업데이 트를 변경됩니다
so right now we're just implementing the gradient
그래서 지금 우리는 단지 그라데이션을 구현하고
taking the gradient and we're integrating our current position by the
그라데이션을 복용하고 우리는에 의해 우리의 현재 위치를 통합하고
ratings in a date instead we're going to take the gradient that we computed and
날짜에 등급 대신 우리는 우리가 계산 된 그라데이션을거야 및
instead of integrating the position directly
대신 직접 위치를 통합
we're going to increment this variable V which I could leave for velocity so
우리는 내가 너무 속도로 떠날 수있는이 변수 V를 증가거야
we're going to see why that is in a bit so we increment
우리는 우리가 증가 그래서 약간의 이유를 보게 될 것입니다
velocity variable be and instead instead we're basically building up this
속도의 변수가 될 대신 대신에 우리는 기본적으로 가입이 구축하고
exponential some credence in the past and that's what integrating the position
과거에 일부 신빙성을 지수 및 그 위치를 통합하는거야
this new here is a happy primer and mute as kind of a number between 0 and one
여기에이 새로운는 0과 1 사이의 숫자의 종류로 행복 프라이머 및 음소거입니다
and was doing it became the previous be and adding on the screen gradient so
그리고 이전 BE되었다 하 등 화면 구배에 첨가 하였다
what's nice about the momentum updated you can interpret it in a very physical
당신은 매우 물리적으로 해석 할 수있는 업데이트 모멘텀에 대한 좋은 데요
terms and in the following way basically using momentum update corresponds to
조건 및 다음과 같은 방법으로 기본적으로 모멘텀 업데이트에 해당하는 사용
interpreting discount list as really a bold rolling allows this round is
할인 목록을 해석하는 정말 대담한 구름이 라운드가 허용하는
landscape and the gradient in this case is your forest that the particles
프리이 경우 그래디언트가 숲이라는 입자
feeling so this article is feeling some force you to gradient instead of
느낌 그래서이 문서는 대신 그라데이션 약간의 힘을 느끼고있다
directly integrating the position this force in physics so force is equivalent
힘이 상당하므로 직접 위치를 물리학이 힘을 통합
to acceleration there and so acceleration is what we're competing and
이 때문에 가속에 가속이 우리가 경쟁하고있는 것입니다
so the velocity gets integrated by the acceleration here and then the new times
그래서 속도는 여기에 다음 새 배의 가속도에 의해 통합됩니다
he has the interpretation of friction in that case because it every single
그 경우에, 마찰의 해석을 가지고 그 때문에 매
iteration were slightly slowing down and intuitively if this new times be was not
반복은 약간 둔화이 새로운 시간이 될 직관적 경우 아니었다했다
there then does bold with never come to rest because it was just around the law
그냥 법 주위에 있었기 때문에 휴식을 오지로 다음 굵게가 않습니다
surface forever and there will be no loss of energy where it would settle at
영원히 표면과가에 정착 할 에너지의 손실이 없을 것
the end of a loss function and so that the momentum update is taking this
손실 기능 등 최종 운동량 업데이트는이 중임
physical interpretation of optimization but we have a ball rolling around around
최적화의 물리적 해석 그러나 우리는 볼이 약 롤링이
and it's slowing down over time and so the way this works is what's very nice
그리고 시간이 지남에 따라 둔화 것 등이 작동하는 방식은 아주 좋은 무엇이다
about this update as you end up building up this velocity and in particular in
이 업데이트에 대한 당신은 특히이 속도와를 구축 끝으로
the shallow directions is very easy to see that if you have a shallow but
얕은 방향을보고 매우 쉽게 당신이 얕은이있는 경우 만
consistent direction then the momentum update will slowly build up the velocity
일관된 방향은 다음 모멘텀 업데이트는 천천히 속도를 구축 할 것입니다
vector in the direction you end up speeding up and up across the shallow
당신이 얕은에서 위로 가속화 결국 방향 벡터
direction but in a very steep directions what's going to happen is you start of
방향하지만 무슨 일이 일어날 매우 가파른 방향으로 당신의 시작입니다
course generally around but then you're always being pulled up the other
과정은 일반적으로 약하지만 당신은 항상 다른 사람을 뽑아되고있어
direction toward the center and with the damping and the kind of oscillating to
중심을 향해 및 감쇠 및 진동의 종류와 방향
the middle and so it's kind of denting these oscillations in a steep directions
그래서 그것은 종류의 가파른 방향이 진동을 찍힌 것 중간 및
and it's kind of encouraging it's encouraging process and is consistent
종류의이 과정을 장려하고 일관성이있어 고무적
shallow directions and that's why it ends up improving the convergence in
얕은 방향과는 컨버전스의 개선 끝나는 이유입니다
many cases so for example here in this visualization we see the SED update in
대부분의 경우는 그래서 여기 시각화, 예를 들어 우리는 SED 업데이트에서 참조
momentum update isn't green and so you can see what happens with the green one
모멘텀 업데이트는 녹색 아니고, 그래서 당신은 녹색 하나를 어떻게 볼 수 있습니다
hit over shoes because it built up all this publicity
신발을 통해 공격하면이 모든 홍보를 구축하기 때문에
overshoots the minimum but then it eventually ends up converting gallon and
최소 오버 슈트하지만 그것은 결국 갤런 변환 끝과
of course it's over shot but once it emerges there you can see that it's
물론 그것은 촬영 끝났어하지만이 나온다 일단 당신은 그것의 것을 볼 수있다
converging there much quicker than just basic as did the update to end up
가 결국 업데이트처럼 그냥 기본보다 훨씬 더 빨리 수렴
building up too much of a statement than you eventually get there quicker than if
문을 너무 많이 구축하면 결국 경우보다가 빨리 얻을 것보다
you did not have the velocity got the momentum update are going to a
당신은 속도가 모멘텀 업데이트는 가고있다있어하지 않았다
particular variation of the momentum appeared in a bit I just wanted to ask
운동량의 특정 변이 난 그냥 물어보고 싶은게 조금 등장
questions about the momentum updates when I got a single like a primer and
나는 프라이머와 같은 단일있어 언제 모멘텀에 대한 질문은 업데이트
usually it takes some values of roughly 8.5 4.9 and usually people sometimes
보통 때때로 어떤 약 8.5 4.9의 값과 보통 사람들 소요
it's not super comet but people sometimes in the lead from 25 2.99
그것은 슈퍼 혜성은 아니지만 사람들이 때때로 리드 (25) 2.99에서
slowly over time but it's just a single number
천천히 시간이 지남에 있지만, 그것은 단지 하나의 숫자입니다
yes so you can avoid those with a smaller learning rate but then the issue
네 그래서 당신은 작은 학습 속도하지만 문제가있는 사람을 방지 할 수 있습니다
is if you had a slower learning rate is applied globally to all directions in
당신이 있다면 느린 학습 속도는 모든 방향에 전 세계적으로 적용된다
the gradient and so then you would basically do no progress in the
그라데이션 등은 당신이에 진전을하지 않는다 기본적 것이다
horizontal direction right you wouldn't get as much but then it would take you
수평 방향으로 오른쪽 당신은 많은 것을 얻을 수 없겠죠하지만 그것은 당신을 데려 갈 것이다
forever to go horizontally few small learning says this kind of trade off
영원히 갈 수평으로 몇 가지 작은 학습은 떨어져 무역의이 종류는 말한다
their selected describe a modification on the question is how to initialize
자신의 질문에 수정을 설명하는 선택 방법을 초기화하는 방법입니다
lost you usually 10 and it doesn't matter too much because you end up
일반적으로 10을 상실하고 결국 있기 때문에 문제가 너무 많이하지 않습니다
building it up in the first few steps and then you end up like this if you
처음 몇 단계를 구축하고 당신은 당신이 경우 다음과 같이 끝
spend out this recurrence you'll see that basically it's exponentially
이 기하 급수적으로의 당신은 기본적으로 그 볼이 재발을 지출
decaying some of your previous greetings and so once you've got it up to you you
이전 인사의 일부를 부패 그래서 당신은 당신이 당신에게 그것을 가지고 한 번
have certain 10 so particular variation of momentum has got something called
모멘텀의 특정 열 때문에 특히 변화라는 것을 가지고있다
mister on momentum and gradient descent and the idea here is we have the
모멘텀과 그라데이션 하강 여기에 생각에 아저씨는 우리가이입니다
ordinary momentum equation here and the way to think about it is that your
보통 운동량 여기 방정식 그것에 대해 생각하는 방법이다 당신의
excess recommended by really two parts
초과 정말 두 부분으로 추천
there's a part of that you build up some momentum in a particular direction so
특정 방향으로 약간의 힘을 너무 구축하는 것이의 한 부분이있다
that's the momentum step in green that's the new times and that's where the
즉, 새로운 시대를 그린의 모멘텀 단계이고 그 곳이다
momentum is currently trying to carry you and then you have the second
모멘텀은 현재를 수행하기 위해 노력하고 두 번째가
contribution from the gradients the gradient is pulling you this way towards
그라디언트에서 기여 기울기는이 방법으로 당기는
the decrease of a loss function and the actual step ends up being the vector sum
손실 함수의 감소와 실제 단계는 벡터 합인 끝낸다
of the two so the blue as much you end up with is just the green plus the red
그래서 블루만큼 당신이 결국 두 사람은 그냥 녹색 더하기 빨간색의
and the idea but necessary momentum and this ends up working better in practice
생각하지만 필요한 모멘텀이 실제로 더 나은 작업 끝과
as the following we know at this point regardless of what the current input was
다음과 같이 우리는 관계없이 현재의 입력이 무엇의이 시점에서 알
to us so we haven't competed against up yet but we know that we've built up some
우리에게 그래서 우리는 최대 아직 대해 경쟁하지 않은 그러나 우리는 우리가 어떤을 구축 한 것을 알고있다
momentum and we know we're definitely going to take this green direction ok so
모멘텀과 우리는 우리가 확실히 확인 그래서이 녹색 방향을거야 알고
we're definitely going to take this Green Valley ingredient here at our
우리는 확실히 여기이 그린 밸리 성분을거야 우리
current spot Nesterov momentum does wants to look ahead and instead
현재의 자리 네 스테 로프 모멘텀을 수행 앞서 대신보고 싶어
evaluates the gradient at this point this point at the top of the arrow so
화살표의 상단이 시점에서이 시점 기울기를 평가하므로
what you end up with is the following difference here we know we're going to
당신이와 끝까지 우리가 우리가가는거야 알고 여기에 다음과 같은 차이
go this way anyway so why not just like look ahead to get to that part of the
왜 그냥 같은 것은 그 부분에 도착하기 앞서 살펴 어쨌든이 길을 갈
objective and evaluate the green at that point and it doesn't of course you're
객관적이고 그 시점에서 녹색을 평가하고 그것은 물론 당신이있어하지 않습니다
reading is going to be slightly different because you're in a different
다른에이기 때문에 독서는 다소 차이가있을 것입니다
position in Los function and this one step ahead give you a slightly better
로스 함수의 위치와이 한 단계 앞서 당신에게 약간 더 나은를 제공
direction
방향
over there and get it a slightly different update now you can do you can
저기 수 있습니다 당신은 당신이 할 수있는 지금 그것을 약간 다른 업데이 트를 얻을
theoretically show that this actually enjoys better theoretical guarantees on
이론적으로이 사실에 더 나은 이론 보장을 즐기는 것을 보여
convergence rates but not only is a true in theory but also in practice and
수렴 속도뿐만 아니라이 이론뿐만 아니라 실제의 사실과
almost always works better than just a moment to ok so the difference roughly
거의 항상 차이가 너무 좋아 그냥 순간보다 더 잘 작동 약
is the following year I've written like like notations that of code but we still
다음 해에 그 코드를하지만 여전히 우리의 표기법처럼 같은 작성한된다
have the time
시간이
mutants the previous velocity vector and the gradient that you're currently
당신이 현재하고있는 이전의 속도 벡터 및 구배를 돌연변이
evaluating and then we do an update here and so the necessary update the only
평가하고 우리는 여기에 업데이트를하고 있으므로 필요한 업데이트 만을
differences were pending here this new plus new times bTW minus 11 will
차이는이 새로운 더한 새로운 BTW 시간을 뺀 11의 뜻 여기 보류했다
evaluate the gradient we have evaluated at a slightly different position in this
우리는이에 약간 다른 위치에서 평가 한 그라데이션을 평가
look ahead to position and so that's really in the strong momentum it almost
위치를 미리보고 그래서 강한 모멘텀에 정말 그것은 거의
always works that are now there's a slight technology here which I don't
항상 지금 약간의 기술은 내가 안되는 여기 거기되는 작품
think I'm going to go into too much but it's slightly inconvenient the fact that
너무 많이 들어갈 것 같네요하지만 사실 그 불편할 약간 있어요
normally we think about just going forward and backward pass so what we end
일반적으로 우리는 향후에 대해 생각하고 뒤로 우리는 결국 무엇 때문에 통과
up with is we have a primary victories data and the gradient at that point but
으로는 최대 프라이 머리 승리 데이터와 그 때의 기울기를 갖지만
you're never off wants us to have a breeding parameters and gradient at a
당신은 떨어져에서 사육 매개 변수 및 그라데이션을 가지고 우리를 원하는 경우는 없습니다
different point so doesn't quite fit in with like a simple API between only
다른 점은 그래서 꽤 단지 사이의 간단한 API처럼에 맞지 않는
having your code and so turns out that there's a way and I don't want to really
코드를 갖는 그래서 방법이 밝혀 내가 정말하고 싶지 않아
probably spent too much time on this but there's a way to basically do a variable
아마이에 너무 많은 시간을 소비하지만, 기본적으로 변수를 할 수있는 방법이
transformer get the notice the beefy you do some rearrangement and then you get
변압기는 통지 일부 재배치를 수행 살이 찐를 얻을 당신은 얻을
something that looks much more like of the newly updated that you can just
더욱 새로 업데이트의처럼 보이는 뭔가 그냥 수
swipe in from Amanda Martin swapping impressed ed because you end up with
당신이 결국 때문에 감동 에드 교환 아만다 마틴에서 스 와이프
only needing gradient atrophy and you up to update something and this feature is
만 그라디언트 위축을 필요로하고 당신을 무언가를 업데이트하고이 기​​능은
really do look ahead
정말 앞서 보여요
version of the parameters since they're just the raw parameter vector that's
매개 변수의 버전들은 그냥 원시 매개 변수 벡터에 있기 때문에
just a technicality you can go into notes to check this out
당신이 노트에 갈 수있는 단지 전문적이 체크 아웃하기
ok so here Nesterov accelerated reading is in magenta and you can see the
확인 그래서 여기에 네 스테 로프 가속 독서는 마젠타에 당신은 볼 수 있습니다
original momentum here over shop but not a lot but because mister of accelerating
원래 가게를 통해 여기 모멘텀하지만 많은하지만 가속 때문에 아저씨
momentum has this one step ahead you'll see that it's curls around much more
모멘텀은 당신이 주위에 더 많은 곱슬 있다고 볼 수 있습니다 앞서이 한 단계가
quickly and that's because all these tiny contributions of a slightly better
신속하고 그 때문에 모든이 작은 기여 약간 더 낫다
gradient at where you're about to be end up adding up and you almost always
당신이하려고합니다 어디에서 그라데이션 합산 결국하고 거의 항상합니다
converge faster so that's necessary so until recently as UD momentum was the
UD 모멘텀이이었다 최근까지 수 있도록 빠른 그래서 필요의 수렴
standard default way of training commercial networks and many people
훈련 상용 네트워크와 많은 사람들의 표준 기본 방법
still trained using just a moment to update this is a common thing to see in
아직이에서 볼 수있는 일반적인 일 업데이트하기 위해 잠시를 사용하여 훈련
practice and even better if necessary
연습과 필요한 경우 더 나은
so mag here stands for a week
그래서 잡지는 여기에 일주일을 의미합니다
question you're thinking about that so i think it's slightly incorrect to was
당신이 그것에 대해 생각하는지 질문은 그래서 나는 그것이 약간 잘못된 생각
only think about a lot of options for neural networks usually think about
만 일반적으로 생각 신경 네트워크에 대한 옵션을 많이 생각
these crazy ravines and lots of local minima everywhere it's actually not a
이 미친 계곡과 지역 최소값을 많이 사방 실제로는 아니다
correct way to look at it that's a correct approximation to have conceptual
그것은 그 보는 올바른 방법은 개념이 할 수있는 올바른 접근이다
in your mind when you have a very small neural networks and people used to think
당신의 마음에 당신은 아주 작은 신경 네트워크와 사람들이 생각하는 데 사용 때
that local minima an issue and optimizing networks but actually turns
지역 최소값 것을 문제 및 최적화 네트워크 그러나 실제로집니다
out with a lot of recent theoretical work that as you scale up your models
당신이 당신의 모델을 확장으로 최근의 이론적 작업의 많은 아웃
these local minimum has become less and less of an issue so that the picture to
이 지역의 최소 갈수록 문제의 사진에 있도록되어 있습니다
have in mind is there are lots of local minima but they're all about the same
생각하고있는 것은 지역의 최소값 많이있다하지만 그들은 같은에 대한 모든 것
actually loss that's a better way to look at it so these functions neural
실제로이 때문에 이러한 기능의 신경을보고 더 나은 방법 손실
networks actually in practice and i'm looking much more like like a bowl
실제로 연습 네트워크와 나는 그릇 등 같은 훨씬 더 찾고 있어요
instead of the crazy ravine landscape and you can show that as you still up
대신 미친 계곡 풍경과 당신은 여전히​​ 당신으로 그것을 표시 할 수 있습니다
the neural network the difference between like the worst than your best
신경망 최선보다는 최악의 등의 차이
local minima
지역 최소값
actually kinda like shrinks down over time with some researchers also
실제로 좀 좋아도 일부 연구자와 시간이 지남에 따라 아래로 축소
basically there's no bad local minima this only happens in very small networks
기본적으로이 매우 소규모 네트워크에서 일어나는 나쁜 지역 최소값가 없습니다
so and in fact in practice what you find is if you initialize with different
당신이 다른과 초기화하면 그렇게 연습에서 실제로 당신이 찾는 것은
random initialization almost always end up getting the same answer like the same
임의의 초기화는 거의 항상 같은처럼 같은 대답을 받고 결국
loss in the end so you don't end up there's no like bad local minima you
결국 손실은 그래서 당신은 같은 나쁜 지방의 최소값은 없습니다 결국하지 마십시오
sometimes especially when you have begun networks question with a question
때로는 특히 당신이 질문을 네트워크 질문을 시작했다 때
Nesterov as an oscillating feature which part
네 스테 로프 진동 기능을하는 부분으로
ok I think you're jumping had maybe by by several slides were going to go into
확인 당신이 여러 슬라이드로 이동하려고했다가에 의해 아마했다 점프 있다고 생각
second or two methods in a bit okay let me jump into another update that is very
약간의 두 번째 또는 두 가지 방법이 괜찮 날 정말 또 다른 업데이트에 뛰어 보자
common to see in practice it's called a ground and it was originally developed
이 접지라고하고 원래 개발 된 사례에서 볼 것이 일반적
in a convex optimization literature and then it was kind of ported over to
다음 볼록 최적화 문학과는 가지에 포팅되었다
neural networks and people sometimes use it so the other great update looks as
다른 큰 업데이트로 보이는 있도록 신경망 사람들은 가끔 사용
follows
다음
we have this update as we normally see some basic stochastic gradient descent
우리가 일반적으로 몇 가지 기본적인 확률 그라데이션 하강을 참조로 우리는이 업데이트가
here learning great times here
여기에 여기에 큰 시간을 학습
gradient but now we're scaling this gradient but this additional variable
그라데이션하지만 지금 우리는이 그라데이션 있지만이 추가 변수를 확장하고
that we keep accumulating note here that this cash which were building up and is
우리는 있었다이 현금 구축하고 있음을 여기에 메모를 축적 유지하는 것이
the sum of gradient square this cache contains positive numbers only
그라데이션 사각형의 합이 캐시는 양수 만 포함
and note that the cache variable here is a joint venture of the same size as your
여기 캐시 변수가 같은 크기의 합작 투자 참고하여
primary factor and so this cash and up building up in a personal dimension were
개인 차원에서 구축 요인 등이 현금과 최대이었다
keeping track of the sum of squares of the gradients or as we like to sometimes
그라디언트 또는 제곱의 합을 추적하는 데 우리는 때때로을에 좋아
called the second moment of those the Oncenter take a moment and so we keep
이들의 두 번째 순간이라는 Oncenter은 잠시 시간을내어 그래서 우리는 계속
building up this cash and then we divide element why's this step function by the
이 현금을 구축하고 우리가 요소를 분할하는 이유에 의해이 단계 기능입니다
square root of cash and so what ends up happening here so that's the reason that
그 이유는 그래서 광장 현금의 루트 그래서 무슨 일이 일어나고 끝이
people call it a purr purr parameter adaptive learning rate method because
사람들은 그것을 푸르르의 푸르르 매개 변수 적응 학습 율법 때문에 호출
every single product every single dimension of your parameter space now
모든 단일 제품 이제 매개 변수 공간의 모든 단일 차원
has its own kind of like learning rate that is scaled dynamically based on what
동적으로 내용에 따라 조정됩니다 같은 학습 속도의 자신의 종류가
kinds of ingredients are seeing in terms of their scale so with this
재료의 종류이 너무 그 규모면에서 볼 수있다
interpretation what happens with autograph in this particular case if we
우리의 경우 특히이 경우 사인으로 발생하는 해석
do this what happens in the horizontal and vertical direction but this kind of
이 어떤 수평 및 수직 방향으로 발생하지만,이 종류의 작업을 수행
dynamics
역학
what you'll see as we have a large gradient vertically and that large
우리가 수직으로 큰 것을 큰 경사를 가지고 당신은 무엇을 볼 수 있습니다
gradient will be added up to cash and then we end up dividing by larger and
그라데이션은 현금까지 추가되고 우리는 더 크고로 나누어 결국
larger numbers so will get smaller and smaller updates in the vertical step so
큰 숫자는 너무 너무 수직 단계에서 더 작은 업데이트를 얻을 것이다
since we're seeing lots of large regions very clean this will decayed learning
우리는 매우 깨끗 큰 영역을 많이보고있는 때문에이 학습을 부패한다
rate and will make smaller and smaller steps in the vertical direction but in
속도가 수직 방향뿐만에서 더 작은 단계들을 만들
the horizontal direction it's a very shallow direction so we end up with
우리가 끝낼 수 있도록 수평 방향으로는 매우 얕은 방향의
smaller numbers in denominator and you'll see that the relative to the Y
분모 작은 숫자는 당신이 볼 수 있다는 Y에 대한 상대
dimension we're going to end up making faster progress so we have this equalize
치수는 우리가이 성능 조정이 있도록 빠른 진행을 끝낼거야
the effect of accounting for this the steepness and inshallah directions you
이 회계의 효과는 기울기와 알라 신의 뜻 방향을 당신에게
can actually have much larger learning right then instead of the vertical
실제로 수직 대신 바로 그때 훨씬 더 큰 학습을 할 수 있습니다
directions and but so that's one problem without a grad is think about what
방향 및하지만 그래서는 대학원이없는 한 문제이다는 생각이 무엇인지
happens to the step size as we're updating this position if we want to
우리가 원한다면 우리는이 위치를 업데이트하고, 상기 공정 크기로 발생
train an entire deep neural network the stakes for a long time and we're
오랜 시간 동안 전체 깊은 신경망에게 지분을 훈련하고 우리는있어
training this summer long time what's going to happen in a degree of course so
그래서 물론 정도에 무슨 일이 일어날 이번 여름에 오랜 시간 훈련
your cash end up building up all the time you add all these positive numbers
현금은 이러한 모든 긍정적 인 번호를 추가 모든 시간을 구축 결국
goes into denominator you're literally just the case 20 and you end up stopping
분모에 들어가는 당신은 말 그대로 단지의 경우 20이고 당신은 중지 끝
learning like completely and so that's not so that's ok income tax problems
완전히 같은 학습 및 그래서 그래서 아니에요 확인 소득세 문제입니다
perhaps we just have a bowling just kind of decay down to the optimum and you're
아마도 우리는 그냥 가지 볼링을 최적의 아래로 붕괴 당신이있어
done but in the neural network the stuff is kinda like shuttling around then it's
수행하지만 신경 네트워크에서 물건 그건 좀 다음 주위에 왕복 같다
trying to picture based on that's like a better way to think of it and so this
그에 따라 그림을 시도하는 것은 그래서이 그것을 생각하고 더 좋은 방법처럼
thing needs continuous kind of energy to get your data and so you don't want to
것은 당신의 데이터를 얻을 에너지의 지속적인 종류를 필요로하고 그래서 당신은 싶지 않아
just decay to a halt so there's a very simple change to an autographed that was
이었다 사인에 매우 간단한 변화가 그래서 그냥 중단 붕괴
proposed by Jeff Hinton recently and the idea here is that instead of keeping
최근 제프 힌튼에 의해 제안 여기 아이디어는 대신 유지하는 것입니다
completely just a sum of squares and I was able to mention weekend we make that
완전히 그냥 제곱의 합과 나는 우리가 있는지 확인 주말을 언급 할 수 있었다
counter a leaky counter so instead we end up with this decay rate hike the
새는 카운터 카운터 그래서 대신에 우리는 하이킹이 붕괴 속도와 끝까지
primary which we set to something like 0.99% squares but the sum of squares is
주 우리는 0.99 % 사각형과 같은 설정 만 제곱의 합이다
leaking slowly but that's ok so we we still maintain this nice equalizing
천천히 누출하지만 괜찮 것은 그래서 우리는 여전히 좋은 동점을 유지하는 우리
effect of equalizing the step sizes in steep or shelling directions
가파른 또는 포격 방향으로 스텝 크기를 등화 효과
we're not going to just convert completely 20 updates that sold arms
우리는 단지 무기를 판매 완전히 20 업데이트를 변환하지 않을거야
prop 19 is historical contact about Armas proper way is the way was
19 법안 무기 적절한 방법에 대한 역사적 접촉하는 방식이었다입니다
introduced to us
우리에게 소개
you think that it would be a paper that proposed this method but in fact it was
당신은이 방법을 제안 종이 될 것이라고 생각하지만 사실 그것은이었다
a slide and Justin Scott Sarah class just a few years ago and so Justin just
슬라이드 저스틴 스콧 사라 클래스 불과 몇 년 전 그래서 저스틴 단지
was giving this Corsair class and flashed a slide of life this is
삶의 슬라이드이되어 번쩍이 해적 클래스를 제공 하였다
unpublished but this usually works well in practice and do this and it's
게시되지 않은 그러나 이것은 일반적으로 실제로 잘 작동하고 이렇게하고 있어요
basically our math problem and so I implemented it then I saw like better
기본적으로 우리의 수학 문제는 그래서 나는 그 다음 내가 더 잘 같은 본 구현
results on my optimization right away and I thought that was really funny and
바로 내 최적화 결과와 나는 그 정말 재미라고 생각하고
so in fact mike in papers not only my papers but many other papers of people
논문뿐만 아니라 내 논문하지만 많은 사람들 다른 논문에서 사실 마이크에 너무
have cited slide from Coursera just slide lecture 6 the slide just this
코 세라에서 슬라이드를 인용 한 바로 강의 6 슬라이드 그냥 밀어
problem since then this is actually now an actual paper and there's more results
이후 문제는 다음이 지금 실제로 실제 용지이며 더 많은 결과가있다
on exactly what he's doing and and so on but for a while this was really funny
정확히 그가하고있어 및 등등하지만 잠시 동안이 정말 우스웠다에
and so in this up my perspective we can see the ground here is blue and Aramis
그래서이까지 내 관점에서 우리는 여기 땅이 파란색과 아라미스입니다 볼 수 있습니다
prop is this
소품이입니다
and black and we can see that both of them covered quite quickly down here
블랙 우리는 둘 다 아래로 여기 아주 빨리 덮여 있음을 알 수
this way in this particular case at a grad and converting slightly faster than
보다 약간 빠른 변환이 대학원에서이 특정한 경우에 방법과
Armas problem but that's not always the case something usually what you see in
무기 문제 그러나 그것은 항상 당신이 볼 일반적으로 어떤 경우 뭔가 아니다
practice when you train to Penn Jillette works as a grad stops too early and are
대학원 너무 일찍 중지하고 그대로 실천하면 펜 Jillette에 훈련 작품
miserable end up usually the winning out in these these methods and questions
비참 말까지 일반적으로 이러한 이러한 방법 및 질문에서 승리
about our most prob go ahead
우리의 가장 확률값은 진행에 대해
the issue is very steep directions you probably don't want to this method is
이 방법은에 문제가 매우 가파른 길 당신은 아마하지 않으려한다
saying to make very fast updates in that direction so yourself down so maybe in
자신 다운 그래서 어쩌면에서 그 방향으로 매우 빠르게 업데이트 할 말
this particular case you'd like to go faster but you're kind of reading into
당신이 좋아하는 것 특히이 경우 빠른 이동하지만 당신은 가지에 읽고
this particular example and that's not true kind of in general and these
이 특정 예 그것은 일반적으로 이들의 진정한 종류 아니다
optimization landscape that no networks are made up of a good strategy to apply
어떤 네트워크가 좋은 전략의 구성되지 않은 최적화 풍경 적용
in those cases in the beginning
처음에 이러한 경우에
oh by the way I skipped over this exploration of 17 but you guys can
오 그런데 나는 17이 탐사를 통해 건너하지만 너희들은 할 수
hopefully see that 127 is there just to prevent the division by zero it's moving
희망 (127)가 움직이는 0으로 나누기를 방지하기 위해 단지가 있음을 볼 수
back to its high proprietor usually we sat at two one five or six or seven or
다시 높은 소유주에 일반적으로 우리는이 1 ~ 5 또는 6 ~ 7 개에 앉아
something like that in the beginning your cash is 0 so then you can come into
시작하여 현금처럼 뭔가 그래서 다음에 올 수 0
your life learning rate 22 what you get is this adaptive behavior but the scale
당신이 무엇을 얻을 당신의 생활 학습 속도 (22)이 적응 행동하지만 스케일입니다
of it is still in your control the absolute scale of it distilling or
이 증류 그것의 절대 규모가 컨트롤에 아직도의 또는
control is still learning rate this story just interrupt its kind of thing
컨트롤은 여전히​​이 이야기는 단지 물건의 종류를 방해 속도를 배우고
can look at more like a relative thing with respect to different primers how
다른 프라이머 방법에 대해 상대적인 것 같은 더 볼 수 있습니다
are you equalizing the steps but absolute global step is still up to you
당신은 단계 동점 골을하지만 절대 글로벌 단계는 최대 아직있다
from the very beginning so effectively doing what you're describing right
아주 당신이 바로 설명하는 일을 매우 효율적으로부터의
because it ends up for getting sort of ingredients from very long time ago and
이 전 아주 긴 시간에서 재료의 종류를 얻기 위해 끝 때문에
it's only really its expression at time t is only a function of the last few
정말 시간 t에서의 발현은 지난 몇의 기능 만있어
ingredients but in an exponentially decaying weighted sum up we're going to
재료는하지만, 지수 함수 적으로 감쇠 가중 합에 우리가 갈거야
go into last update glad
다행 마지막 업데이트로 이동
would be similar to exponentially weighted way and so you want to have a
기하 급수적으로 가중 방식과 유사하고 그래서 당신은이 할 것
finite window on this or I don't think people have really tried you can ya
나는 사람들을 생각하지 않습니다 또는이에 유한 창 정말 당신에게 나중에 할 수 있습니다 시도
takes too much memory when you're 10 optimizing networks will see that X for
당신이 10 최적화 네트워크있을 때를 위해 그 X를 볼 것이다 너무 많은 메모리를 필요
example 240 million parameters so that's taking up quite a lot of memory and so
예되도록 240,000,000 매개 변수의 메모리가 꽤 많이 복용하고 그래서
you don't want to keep track of 10 previous grievances well okay then we're
당신은 우리가있어 다음도 좋아 (10) 이전의 불만을 추적하고 싶지 않아
gonna go in 20 sure if you combine a degraded momentum thank you for the
거하면 성능이 저하 된 모멘텀을 결합하면 20 있는지에 가서 주셔서 감사합니다
question and that's the slide so so roughly what's happening is Adam is this
질문이 너무 너무 대충 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 슬라이드의 아담이을이다
last update was only prison actually proposed very recently and it has
마지막 업데이트는 감옥 실제로 최근에 제안되었다 그리고있다
elements of both as you'll notice momentum is kind of keeping track of the
당신이 기세를 알 수 있습니다로 모두의 요소는 가지의 트랙을 유지하고있다
first order moment of your of your reading that sums up the wrong gradients
잘못된 그라디언트를 요약하여 독서의의 첫 번째 순서의 순간
and keeping this exponential some and a grandson are keeping track of the second
이 지수 일부와 손자를 유지하는 두 번째의 트랙을 유지하고 있습니다
moment the gradient and and what you end up with is Adam Adam update as you end
순간 기울기와 당신이 종료 아담 아담 업데이트 당신이와 끝까지이다
up with the step that's basically take it's kind of like yeah it's kind of like
기본적으로의 단계와 그것의 같은 종류의 것이 네 같은 종류의 수행
our most probably momentum a bit so you end up with this thing that looks like
조금 그래서 당신처럼 보이는이 일을 끝낼 가장 아마 모멘텀
it's basically keep track of this velocity in a decaying way and that's
그것은 기본적으로 부패 방법이 속도를 추적 그리고 그건
your step but then you also scaling it down by this exponentially adding up
당신의 단계하지만 당신은이 기하 급수적까지 추가하여 아래로 확장
leaky counter of your square gradients and so you end up with both in the same
새는 당신의 광장 그라디언트의 카운터 등 동일한에서 모두 끝
formula and thats update combining those do so you're doing both momentum and
공식과 사람들은 그래서 당신이 모두 힘을 다하고 않는 조합 그게 업데이트 및
you're also doing this adaptive scaling and let see so here's the army's prob
당신은 또한이 적응 스케일링을하고있는 그래서 여기에있는 군대의 확률값하자
actually I should have flashed this earlier so even when compared this
이를 비교했을 때 실제로 정말 심지어이 이전 버전을 번쩍해야
basically our most prob
기본적으로 가장 확률값
red is the same thing as here except we've replaced TX which there was just a
빨간색은 여기에 우리가 대체 한 것을 제외하고는 동일한 것입니다 단지가 있었다 TX
previous just a gradient currently right now we're replacing this gradient TX
이전 단지 그라데이션 현재 지금 우리는이 그라데이션 TX를 교체하고
with it
그것으로
which is this running counter of RDX so if you imagine for example one way to
예를 한 가지 방법에 대한 상상 그래서 만약 RDX이 실행 카운터 인
look at it also is your nasty kasich setting your sampling many batches
또한 샘플링 많은 배치를 설정하여 불쾌한 kasich입니다 그것을 보면
there's gonna be lots of randomness in a poor pass and you get all these noisy
야이 나쁜 패스 난수의 많은 수 그리고 당신은이 모든 잡음을 얻을 수있어
gradients so instead of using any great impact every single time step we're
그라디언트 그래서 대신에 우리가있어 매번 단계를 어떤 큰 영향을 사용하여
actually going to be using this became some of previous greetings and it can
실제로 이전 인사의 일부가되었고, 그것을 할 수있는 사용하는 것
stabilize your gradient direction of it and that's the function of the momentum
그것의 그라디언트 방향을 안정시키고 그 기세의 기능입니다
here and the scaling here is to make sure that the step-size workout relative
여기와 여기에 스케일링이 있는지 확인하는 것입니다 스텝 크기의 운동에 대하여
to each other and Steven L directions thank you don't want to be that you are
서로 스티븐 L 방향이 감사에 당신은 당신이 것을 싶지 않아
hyper parameters
하이퍼 매개 변수
801 usually point 9802 usually Point 995
(801)는 일반적으로 보통 9802 포인트 995 가리
somewhere there so it's a high premium across a leader in my own work I found
내 자신의 일에 선두에 걸쳐 높은 프리미엄을의 어딘가에있을 정도로 나는 발견
that this is a relatively robust settings across I don't actually usually
내가 실제로 일반적으로하지 않습니다에 걸쳐이 상대적으로 강력한 설정입니다
end up leaving these I just set them to put smileys usually but you can play
이러한 난 그냥 보통 스마일을 넣어으로 설정 떠나 결국하지만 당신은 재생할 수 있습니다
with those of it and sometimes it can help you get momentum we saw the
당신이 추진력을 얻을 수 있습니다 그것의 사람들과 때때로 우리는 보았다
restaurant works better clean do that yes you can actually just read the paper
그래 당신은 실제로 단지 용지를 읽을 수 않는 것이 레스토랑 작동 더 나은 청소
about this yesterday and actually wasn't a paper it was a project report from 229
실제로 어제는 종이 아니었다 대해이 229에서 프로젝트 보​​고서이었다
someone actually that that I'm not sure if there's a paper about it but you can
나는 그것에 대해 용지가 있는지 모르겠어요하지만 당신이 할 수있는 것을 실제로 사람
play with that simply does not being done here
즉 단순히 여기에 수행되지 않습니다 놀이
ok and one more thing that I so I have to make Adam slightly more complex here
확인 나는 내가 여기에 아담이 약간 더 복잡하게 할 한 가지 더
as you see it's incomplete so let me just put into complete immersion in Adam
그것은 불완전 당신이 볼 정도로 나를 그냥 아담의 완전한 몰입에 넣어 보자
there's one more thing where you might be confused when you see it there's this
당신이이 거기에 참조 할 때 혼동 될 수 있습니다 한가지 더있다
thing called bias correction to insert their and despise correction the way to
바이어스 보정이라는 것은 자신의 삽입 및 수정을하는 방식을 경멸하는
the reason I'm expanding of the loop is that the bias correction depends on your
I는 루프의 확대 야하는 이유는 바이어스 보정가에 달려 있다는
absolute time step T 00 T is used here and the reason for that is what this is
절대 시간 단계 00 T T 여기에서 사용되며, 그 이유는 이것이 무엇
doing is kind of like a minor point and I don't want to be confused about this
의 작은 점 같은 종류의 일을하고 나는 이것에 대해 혼동하지 않으
too much but basically it's compensated for compensating for the fact that MMV
너무하지만 기본적으로 그 MMV 사실을 보상하기위한 보상있어
ornish 500 statistics are incorrect in the beginning and so what he's doing is
오니 쉬 (500) 통계는 처음에 잘못 그래서 그가 무엇을하고 있는지입니다
really at scaling up your Mb
정말 메가를 확장에서
the first few iterations so you don't end up with a very kind of biased
당신이 편견의 매우 친절와 끝까지하지 않도록 처음 몇 반복
estimate of the first and the second moment so don't worry about that
제 1 및 제 2 순간의 추정은 그래서 그것에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오
too much this is only this is only changing your update at the very first
너무 많은 이것은 단지이 매우 먼저 귀하의 업데이트를 변화한다
few times that's as as the item is warming up and so it's done in a proper
항목 등으로의 몇 번 예열되고, 그래서는 적절한에서 이루어집니다
way in terms of the statistics Mb
통계 메가 측면에서 방법
I don't go too much into that ok so we talked about several different updates
나는 우리가 여러 가지 업데이트에 대한 이야기​​ 그 확인으로 너무 많이 가지 않는다
and we saw that all these updates have this learning great primer still there
우리는 이러한 모든 업데이트가 여전히이 배우는 좋은 프라이머를 보았다
and so I just want to briefly talk about the fact that although still require a
그래서 난 그냥 여전히 필요하지만 것을 간략하게 사실에 대해 얘기하고 싶지
learning and we saw what happens with the front racism learning rates for all
학습과 우리 모두를위한 전면 인종 차별주의 학습 속도로 일어나는 보았다
of these methods and the question i'd like to pose is which one of these
이러한 방법과 내가 제기하고자하는 질문을 다음의 어느 하나
learning rates is best to use
속도를 학습 사용하는 것이 가장 좋습니다
so when you're running neural networks this is a slide about learning rate the
당신이 신경 네트워크를 실행하는 경우 그래서 이것은 레이트 학습에 대한 슬라이드입니다
case the trick answer is that none of those are good learning race to use what
트릭 답을 구분하는 것은 그 중에 무엇을 사용하는 좋은 학습 레이스가 없다는 것입니다
you should do is you should use the high learning rate first because it optimizes
이 최적화 때문에 당신은 당신이 먼저 높은 학습 속도를 사용해야한다해야
faster than the good learning rate is seen you make a very fast progress but
좋은 학습 속도보다 더 빨리 당신이 매우 빠른 진전을 볼 수 있지만,
at some point you're going to be two stochastic and you can't converging to
어떤 점에서 두 확률 될거야 당신은에 수렴 할 수 없습니다
your main my very nicely because you have too much energy in your system and
주 내 아주 잘 당신이 시스템에 너무 많은 에너지를 가지고 있기 때문에
you can't settle down into black nice parts of your loss function and so what
당신은 당신의 손실 함수의 검은 좋은 부품 등 무엇으로 정착 할 수 없습니다
you do then is UDK you're learning rate and then you can kind of ride this
당신은 당신이 속도 배우고 UDK는 다음 종류의이 탈 수 할
dragon of decreasing learning rates and do best in all of them are many
감소 학습 속도의 드래곤과 그들 모두에 최선을 다할가 많다
different ways that people begin to learn rates over time and you should
사람들이 시작하는 다른 방법은 시간이 지남에 따라 요금을 배울 당신은해야
also became your assignment of their stuff decay which is kind of like the
또한 같은 종류의 그들의 물건 붕괴의 과제가되었다
simplest one perhaps or after one epoch of training data is referring to you've
당신이했습니다에 간단한 하나는 아마도 훈련 데이터의 한 시대는 참조 후
seen every single training sample one time so after saying what a Paki decayed
파키스탄 새끼가 부패 무슨 말을 한 후 한 번에 너무 매 훈련 샘플을 볼 수
learning rates to my point nine or something like that you can also use
내 포인트 9 또는 당신은 또한 사용할 수있는 뭔가에 요금을 학습
exponential decay or one of the TDK there several several of them are going
지수 붕괴하거나 여러 거기 TDK 중 하나 여러가는거야
to know it's likely expanding on some of the theoretical properties that improve
그것은 가능성이 향상 이론적 특성의 일부에 확대하고있어 알고
about these different case unfortunately not many of them apply because I think
내가 생각하기 때문에 서로 다른 경우에 대한 그들의 불행하게도 많은하지 적용
they're mostly from convex optimization literature and we're dealing with very
그들은 볼록 최적화 문학에서 대부분이고 우리는 매우 상대하고
different objectives but usually in practice I just used for something that
목표 다르지만 일반적으로 실제로 나는 뭔가에 사용되는
was a question
질문이었다
not committing to any one of these between them during training
훈련 동안 이들 사이의 어느 하나의 커밋되지
yeah I don't think that's the standard at all
그래, 난 그 모든 표준 생각하지 않습니다
an interesting point I'm not sure I'm not sure when you'd want to use yeah
흥미로운 점 나는 당신이 그래 사용할 줄 때 확실하지 않다 확실하지 않다
it's not clear to me you could try something to try and practice I like to
그것은 나에게 분명하지 않다 당신이 시도하고 I가 좋아 연습 뭔가를 시도 할 수 있습니다
make the point that you almost always I find at least impact is right now is
적어도 영향은 바로 지금이다 당신은 거의 항상 내가 발견 지점을
usually the nice default rose to go with so I use a time for everything now and
일반적으로 좋은 기본값은 지금 모든 것을 위해 시간을 사용하므로 함께 갈 장미
seems to work quite well better than momentum are our most problems or
아주 잘 우리의 대부분의 문제는 모멘텀보다 더 나은 또는 작동하는 것 같다
anything like that so it's a tall order methods as we call them because they
그들 때문에 우리가 그들에게 전화로 그런 아무것도 그래서 키가 큰 주문 방법이다
only use your gradient information at your loss function so we've evaluated
우리가 평가 한 있도록 만 손실 함수에 그라디언트 정보를 사용하여
the gradient and we basically know the slope and every single direction and
그라데이션은 우리가 기본적으로 기울기와 모든 단일 방향을 알고
that's the only thing that we use
즉, 우리가 사용하는 유일한 것이다
there's an entire set of second order methods for optimization but you should
이 최적화를위한 2 차 방법의 전체 세트입니다하지만 당신은해야
be aware of the second order opposition as I do want to go into too much detail
내가 너무 많은 세부 사항에 가고 싶지 않는 2 차 반대의 인식
but the end up forming a larger approximation to your loss function so
그러나 결국 최대 그래서 당신의 손실 함수에 더 큰 근사치를 형성
they don't only approximated with this basically hyperplane of like which way I
그들 만이 기본적으로 초평면에 근사하지 않는 방법 I 등
was hoping but you also approximated by discussion which is telling you how your
희망하지만 당신도 토론에 의해 근사 한을 알리는 방법입니다
services curbing so you don't only need the gradient he also need the Hessian
그래서 당신은 그가 또한 독일인 필요한 그라데이션이 필요하지 않습니다 억제 서비스
need to compute that as well and you may have seen you tonight I'd say for
뿐만 아니라 그 계산해야하고 당신에게 내가 말할 것 오늘 밤에 볼지도 모른다
example in 229
229 예
Newton method it's basically giving you an update that was you formed your bowl
뉴턴의 방법은 기본적으로 당신이 그릇을 형성 업데이 트를주고
like fashion approximation to your objective you can use this updated
당신의 목적에 같은 패션 근사이 업데이트 사용할 수 있습니다
number to jump directly to the minimum of that that approximation scheme so
수는 그래서 그 근사 방식의 최소로 직접 이동합니다
what's nice about second order methods why do people like these are used them
어떤이 그들을 사용된다 사람을 왜 2 차 방법에 대한 좋은 데요
especially the Newton method is presented here what's nice about this
특히 뉴턴 방법은 이것에 대해 좋은 무엇을 여기에 제시
update for convergence
컨버전스에 대한 업데이트
you'll notice no learning rate know how primary in this update ok and that's
당신은 학습 속도가 확인이 업데이트의 방법 차 알지 알 수 있습니다 그리고 그건
because if you see your gradient in this loss function in this loss function but
이 손실 기능이 손실 함수에 그라데이션을 보는 경우에 있기 때문에
you also know the curvature and that place and so if you approximated with
당신은 또한 곡률과 그 장소를 알고 당신은 근사 그렇다면
this bull you know exactly where to go to the minimum order approximation so
정확히 알고있는이 황소는 어디에 때문에 최소 주문 근사치로 이동합니다
there's no need for learning you can jump directly to that minimum of that
그의 최소로 직접 이동할 수 있습니다 당신 학습을위한 필요가 없습니다
approximating bowl so that's a very nice feature I think those are the two that I
그게 내가 그 생각 아주 좋은 기능 그래서 그릇에 근접하면 두 가지가 I
had in mind you have a fast convergence because you're using second order
당신은 두 번째 순서를 사용하고 있기 때문에 생각했던 당신은 빠른 수렴을
information as well why is it kind of impractical to use this step update in
뿐만 아니라 정보가 왜이 단계 업데이트를 사용하도록 종류의 불가능하다
training all that works for the issue of course is passion say you have a hundred
과정의 문제에 대한 작품을 모든되는 교육 열정은 백을 말한다
million primary network
만 기본 네트워크
hundred-million by hundred-million matrix and then you want to convert it
백 만 백 만 행렬 그리고 당신은 그것을 변환 할
so good luck with that this is not going to happen so there are several
그이 너무 행운 그래서 몇 가지가 발생하지 않을
algorithms and I just like you to be aware of your not going to use them as
알고리즘과 난 그냥 당신이 당신이 그들을 사용하지 않을 알고 싶습니다
class which is below where there's something called DHS which basically
기본적으로 뭔가 불리는 곳 DHS하는 아래 클래스
lets you get away with not converting the fashion and build up an
수 있습니다 당신은 패션을 변환하지 멀리 얻을 구축
approximation of the Hessian through successive updates that are all ranked
모든 순위 연속 업데이트를 통해 헤센의 근사
one and it kind of builds up the session but you still need to store the Hessian
하나는 그것의 종류의 세션을 구축하지만 당신은 여전히​​ 헤 시안을 저장해야
in memory so still no good for large networks and then there's something
대규모 네트워크에 대한 다음 거기에 뭔가 더 좋은 때문에 여전히 메모리에
called lbs short for limited Jeremy BFGS was not actually store in the fall
제한 제레미 BFGS의 약자라는 파운드 실제로 가을에 저장되지 않았습니다
fashion or it's approximated members and that's what people use in practice
패션 아니면 근사 회원 그리고 그 사람들이 실제로 사용하는 무엇을
sometimes now lbs you'll see sometimes mentioned in optimization literature
때로는 지금 당신은 때때로 최적화 문헌에 언급 참조합니다 LBS
especially when it works really really well for us if you have a single small
그것은 우리를 위해 정말 정말 잘 작동 특히 당신은 작은 하나가있는 경우
deterministic function like a box there's no stochastic noise like there's
이처럼 상자 같은 결정 기능에는 확률 적 노이즈가 없습니다
no city in and everything fits in your memory address can usually crushing loss
과 모든 것을 더 도시는 일반적으로 손실을 분쇄 할 수 있습니다 메모리 주소에 맞는 없다
functions very easily but what's tricky as to extend lbs gs2 basically very very
기능을 아주 쉽게 그러나 아주 아주 기본적 파운드 GS2을 연장으로 까다로운
large datasets and the reason is that were subsampling these many doctors
대규모 데이터 세트 및 이유는이 많은 의사를 서브 샘플링 하였다된다
because we can't fit all the training data into memory so wassup simple many
우리는 많은 그래서 WASSUP에 간단한 메모리에 모든 훈련 데이터를 맞지 않을 수 있기 때문에
batches and then I'll be at risk of works on these many matches and its
배치는 다음 나는이 많은 경기와에 작품의 위험이있을거야 그
approximation is in the being incorrect as you swap different many batches and
근사는 서로 다른 여러 배치를 교환하고 같이있는 잘못에
and also has the capacity you have to be careful with it then you have to make
또한 당신이 조심해야 할 능력을 가지고 당신은 확인해야합니다
sure that you fix a dropout
당신이 드롭 아웃을 수정해야
you have to make sure that your function so internally albeit rascals your
당신이 있는지 확인해야하므로 내부적으로 불량배이기는하지만 함수 당신의
function many many different times is doing all these approximations and lie
기능 많은 많은 다른 시간이 모든 근사하고 거짓말을하고있다
search and stuff like that it's a very heavy function and so you have to make
검색 물건이 매우 무거운 함수의 같은 것을 그래서 당신은 확인해야합니다
sure that when you use this you disable or sources
당신이 사용할 때 사용하지 않거나 출처 확인
randomness because really not going to like it so basically in practice we
랜덤 정말 연습 우리에 그래서 기본적으로 그것을 좋아하지 않을 때문에
don't use all BHS because it seems to not great not worked really well right
큰 잘 못했습니다 정말 일을하지하지 않는 것 때문에 모든 BHS를 사용하지 않는
now compared to other methods is basically to have too much stuff is
지금은 다른 방법에 비해 너무 많은 재료가 갖는 기본적
happening and you it's better to just do this and noisy our stuff but do more of
일이 당신이 더 나은 것은 바로이 우리의 물건을 잡음을하지만 이상을 수행합니다
it that's the trade off so in summary used as a good choice and if you can
당신이 할 수있는 경우 그 거래는 좋은 선택으로 사용 요약 그렇게 꺼져과
afford to just have you can afford for banks to maybe your day as it is not
그렇지 않은으로 당신이 아마 하루에 은행 감당할 수있는 여유
very large income for 2009 memory and the forward and they get passes in
2009 메모리와 앞으로 매우 큰 소득과 그들에 패스를 얻을
memory then you can look into lbs but you won't see it in practice used in
메모리 당신은 파운드로 볼 수 있지만에서 사용 관행에 표시되지 않습니다
large-scale setting right now although its research direction right now right
현재 연구 방향 비록 지금 바로 대규모 설정
so that concludes my discussion of different private updates because you're
당신이이기 때문에 그래서 다른 개인 업데이트의 제 논의를 결론
learning rates we're not going to look into all beatrice in this class there's
학습 속도는 우리가 거​​기에이 클래스의 모든 베아트리체 조사하지 않을거야
a question the very back
바로 다시 질문
you're asking about so a great for example it automatically case you're
당신에 대한 요구하는지 너무 좋은 자동으로 당신이있어 구분 예를 들어
learning rate over time so would you use also learning break the case if you're
그래서 시간이 지남에 속도를 학습 당신은 또한 당신이 있다면 사건을 깰 학습 사용합니다
using a grand or so usually you see learning Reiki very common when you
그래서 일반적으로 그랜드 이상을 사용하면 때를 매우 일반적인 영기를 배우는 참조
actually I'm not sure if you use it but at a grad or or Adam yeah it's it's not
실제로 나는 당신이 대학원 또는 그러나 그것을 사용하는 경우 확실하지 않다 또는 아담 그래 그것은 아닙니다입니다
not not a very good answer that you can certainly do it but maybe item is not
하지 아니 아주 좋은 대답 당신은 그것을 할 확실히 할 수 있지만 어쩌면 항목이 아니라고
like Adam will not just wantonly make your learning 30 at the Android because
아담처럼 그냥 방자 안드로이드 때문에에서 학습 (30)를하지 않습니다
it's a leaky gradient but he was a great concern he became the learning rate
이 새는 그라데이션입니다하지만 그는 학습 속도가 된 큰 우려했다
probably does not make sense because it's decayed automatically 20 Indian
그것은 인도 자동으로 20을 부패 있기 때문에 아마 이해가되지 않습니다
alright okay we're going to go into model ensembles I just very briefly like
괜찮아 괜찮아 우리는 매우 간단하게 같은 모델 앙상블 I에 갈거야
to talk about it because it's quite simple
그것은 아주 간단하기 때문에 그것에 대해 얘기
turns out that if you train multiple independent models on your training data
당신이 당신의 훈련 데이터에 여러 개의 독립적 인 모델을 훈련하면 밝혀
instead of just a single one and then you averaged results at this time you've
대신 다음 단 하나의 하나의 당신은 당신이했습니다이 시간에 결과를 평균
always got 22 percent extra performance ok so this is not really a theoretical
항상 22 % 추가 성능 확인 지금이 정말 이론적하지있어
result here it's kind of like a result but just like in practice
그 결과 같은 종류의하지만 그냥 연습처럼 여기 결과
basically this is like a good thing to do almost always works better
기본적으로이 거의 항상 더 잘 작동 할 좋은 것 같다
the downside of course is not have to have all these different independent
물론 단점은 모든 다른 독립이 필요하지 않습니다
models and need to do forward and backward classes of all of them and you
모델과 앞으로해야 할 필요와 그들과 여러분의 뒤로 클래스
have trained all of them so that's not ideal and presumably you're slow down
그 적합하지 그래서 그들 모두를 훈련 아마 당신은 아래로 느려했다
just time with the number of models in your ensemble and so there are some tips
당신의 앙상블 모델의 수와 단지 시간 등 몇 가지 팁이있다
and tricks for using on some kind of picking up a bit so one approach for
및 유용한 정보 비트를위한 그래서 하나의 접근 방식을 따기 어떤 종류의에 사용
example is as your training your neural network you have all these different
예를 들어 당신이 가진 당신이 당신의 신경망을 훈련으로 모든 서로 다른를
checkpoints usually are saving them every single hockey save a checkpoint
체크 포인트는 일반적으로 체크 포인트를 저장 그들에게 하나 하나 하키를 저장하는
and you figure out what your was your validation performance so one thing you
당신은 당신이 당신의 검증 성능 그래서 한 가지 당신이 무엇인지 알아낼
can do for example it turns out to actually gets like this sometimes is you
실제로 판명 예를 위해 할 수있는 것은 때로는 같은 얻을 당신입니다
just take some different checkpoints on your model and you were those that
당신의 모델에 대한 몇 가지 체크 포인트를 가지고 당신은 그했다 그
actually turns out to sometimes improve things in it and so that way you don't
실제로 때때로에서 사물과 그렇지 그래서 방법을 개선하기 위해 밝혀
have to train seven independent models US-trained one but you ensemble some
한 미국 훈련 칠 독립적 인 모델을 훈련해야하지만 당신은 어떤 앙상블
different checkpoints related to that there's a trick of
그와 관련된 다른 체크 포인트의 트릭있다
protest what's happening here this is your four steps that we've seen before
이것은 우리가 전에 본 적이 당신의 네 단계를 여기에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지에 항의
I'm keeping another set of primaries here X test and this text as a running
나는 실행으로 여기에 예비 선거 X 테스트의 또 다른 세트와이 텍스트를 유지하고있어
some exponentially decaying off my actual parameter vector X and when I use
일부 기하 급수적으로 내 실제 매개 변수 벡터 X를 썩 때 내가 사용하는
text test and validation or test data it turns out that this almost always
텍스트 테스트 및 검증이나 테스트 데이터는 거의 항상이 밝혀
perform slightly better than using X alone ok so this is kind of doing like a
이 때문에 종류의 같이하고있는 단독 확인 X를 사용하는 것보다 약간 더 나은 수행
small like weighted ensemble of last previous few primary factors it's kind
마지막으로 이전 몇 주 요인 작은 같은 가중 앙상블 그것은 종류의
of a kind of difficult to interpret actually but basically one way to
어려운 종류의 한 가지 방법으로 실제로는하지만, 기본적으로 해석하는
interpret it one way I can handle about why this is actually a good thing to do
그것을 나는이 실제로 할 수있는 좋은 일이 이유에 대해 처리 할 수​​있는 하나의 방법을 해석
is think about optimizing your ball function and you're stepping too much
당신의 공 기능을 최적화에 대해 생각하고, 당신은 너무 많은 스테핑있어
around your minimum that actually taking the average of all those steps gets you
실제로 모든 단계의 평균을 복용 최소 당신을 얻을 수 주위에
closer to the minimum ok I can do for why this actually is important slightly
I가 할 수있는 최소한의 확인에 가까운이 실제로 약간 중요한 이유
better so that small ensembles I had to discuss my life because we're going to
더 나은 우리가 가고 있기 때문에 내가 가진 작은 앙상블은 내 인생을 논의하기 위해 수 있도록
look into dropout and this is a very important technique that you will be
드롭 아웃으로 보면 이것은 당신이 될 것입니다 매우 중요한 기술이다
using an implementation and so on so the idea for dropout is very interesting
드롭 아웃에 대한 생각은 매우 흥미로운 그래서 등등 구현 및 사용
what you do with dropout is you as you're doing your whole purpose of
당신의 전체 목적을하고있는 것처럼 당신이 강하와 함께 할 당신입니다
neural network you will randomly set some neurons 20 in the park pass so just
신경 네트워크는 무작위 그래서 그냥 통과 공원에서 일부 뉴런 (20)을 설정합니다
to clarify what you will do is as you're doing a forward pass of your data X your
당신이 당신의 데이터 X의 전진 패스를하고있는 당신이 어떤 작업을 수행하는지 명확히하는 것은 당신의
computing a say in this function
이 기능에 발언권을 계산
your first hidden layer is the nonlinearity of W one times XP sp1 so
첫 번째 숨겨진 층 W의 비선형 하나 배 XP SP1 그래서
that's a little later and then I will compute here a mask of binary numbers
그건 좀 이상이고 다음 여기 이진수의 마스크를 계산합니다
either 0 or 1 based on whether or not
여부에 기초하여 0 또는 1 중
numbers between 0 and one are smaller than P which we hear serious pump so
0과 1 사이 숫자는 우리가 심각한 펌프를 듣고있는 P보다 작은
this you want is a binary mask of zeros and ones half and half and then we
당신이 원하는이 우리는 0과 1의 절반과 절반의 바이너리 마스크입니다
multiply that are hidden activations actively dropping half of them so we
다중 정품 인증 적극적으로 우리가 그들의 절반을 포기 숨겨진되는
computed all the activations each one hidden layer and then we drop have two
모든 정품 인증 각 하나의 숨겨진 레이어를 계산 한 다음 우리는 두 가지가 드롭
units at random and then we do second and then we drop half of them at random
무작위로 유닛, 그리고, 우리는 두 번째, 그리고, 우리는 무작위로 그 중 절반을 드롭 할
ok and of course this is only the forward pass the backward pass has to be
확인 물론 이것은 단지 전방이 후방 패스이어야 합격입니다
appropriately adjusted as well so these drops have to be also back propagated
적절하게이 방울도 다시 전파 할 수 있도록뿐만 아니라 조정
through so remember to do that when you implement drop out so it's not only in
그것에서뿐만 아니라, 그래서 그렇게 통해 구현할 때 중퇴 그렇게 기억
the forward pass a drop but in a backward pass if the backpropagation
전진은 드롭을 통과하지만, 역 전파는 경우 후방 패스
multiplying by u2 and buy you one so you killed radiance basically in places
U2에 의해 곱하면 하나는 그래서 당신이 장소에서 기본적으로 생기를 죽인를 구입
where you dropped
당신은 떨어 곳
ok so you might be thinking when I showed you this for the first time how
나는이 방법을 처음으로 당신이를 보였다 때 확인 그래서 당신은 생각 될 수 있습니다
does this make any sense at all and how was this good idea why would you want to
이 전혀 이해가 않습니다이 좋은 생각은 왜에 어떻게 원하는 것이되었다
compute your neuroses and then set them a trend in 20 make any sense whatsoever
당신의 신경증을 계산하고 (20)이 어떠한 의미를에 다음 그들에게 경향을 설정
so I don't know let's let's do you guys think ahead to prevent overheating in
그래서 나도 몰라 그럼 이제 너희들은 앞서 생각에 과열을 방지 할 수 있도록하자
what sense
어떤 의미
you're really getting the right information so you're saying it will
당신은 정말 당신이 그것을 할 말을하는지 있도록 올바른 정보를 얻고
prevent overfitting because if I'm only using half of my network then roughly I
난 단지 그때 내 네트워크의 절반을 거​​의 사용하고있는 경우 때문에 overfitting을 방지
have like smaller capacity I'm only using half of my network any one time
난 단지 내 네트워크를 한 번의 절반을 사용하고 작은 용량의 같은이
and one smaller networks there's only like I'm basically there's only so much
하나의 작은 네트워크 I 기본적으로 만 너무 거기에있어 단지처럼 거기
I can do what happened at work then there's a full network so it's kind of
이 종류의 그래서 나는 다음 전체 네트워크 거기에 직장에서 무슨 일이 있었는지 수행 할 수 있습니다
like control of your of your variance in terms of what you can represent
당신이 대표 할 수 있는지의 관점에서 당신의 분산 제어 등
yeah I would like to meet the terms of like by various trade often so I haven't
그래 나는 종종 내가하지 않은 다양한 무역에 의해 등의 조건을 충족하고 싶습니다
really we're not going to that too much but you have a smaller model it's harder
정말 우리는 너무 많이하지 않을거야하지만 힘들다는 더 작은 모델을
to over that but having many ensembles of different neural networks were going
그 이상하지만 서로 다른 신경 네트워크의 여러 앙상블을 갖는 것은 가고 있었다
to go into that point in a bit because if that was the only one that was used
즉 사용 된 하나의 경우 때문에 조금에 그 시점으로 이동
upstairs ok I have a better way of phrasing that point in my next life
위층 확인 내 다음 인생에서 가리 말씨의 더 나은 방법이
let's look at a particular example is that okay suppose that we are trying to
의 그 괜찮아 우리가하려고하는 것을 가정하는 특정 예를 살펴 보자
compute the cat score in the neural network and the idea here is that you
신경 네트워크의 고양이 점수를 계산하고 여기에 아이디어는 것입니다
have all these different units and dropout is doing sports sing their many
이러한 모든 다른 단위를 가지고 강하하고있는 스포츠는 많은 노래
way to look at dropout but one of them is it's forcing your code your
방법은 드롭 아웃을보고 있지만 그 중 하나는 당신의 코드 당신의 강요 것입니다
representation for what the image was about to be redundant because you need
어떤 이미지의 표현은 당신이 필요로하기 때문에 중복하고 있었다
that redundancy because you're about to in a way that you can't control get half
그 중복 당신은 당신이 절반을받을 제어 할 수있는 방법에 대해이기 때문에
of your network dropped off and so you need to make your cat score on many more
네트워크의 내려 그래서 당신은 더 많은 당신의 고양이 점수를 확인해야합니다
features if you're going to cook correctly compute the cat score because
기능은 제대로 요리 고양이 점수 때문에를 계산하기 위하여려고하는 경우
any any one of them you can't rely on it because it might be dropped and so
어떤 어떤이 삭제 될 수도 있기 때문에 당신이 그것에 의존 할 수 그들 중 하나 등등
that's one way to look at it so in this case we can still classify catskill
이 경우 우리는 여전히 캐츠 킬을 분류 할 수 있도록 그게 보는 하나의 방법입니다
properly even if we don't have access to whether or not it's very essential so
우리는 매우 중요 그래서 여부에 대한 액세스 권한이없는 경우에도 적절
that's one interpretation of dropout
즉, 드롭 아웃의 하나의 해석이다
another interpretation of dropout is as was mentioned in terms of muscle so
드롭 아웃의 또 다른 해석은 다음과 같이 근육의 관점에서 언급되어,
dropout is effectively can be looked at as training a large ensemble of models
드롭 아웃 효과적으로 모델의 큰 앙상블 훈련으로 바라 보았다 될 수있다
that are basically subnetworks
기본적으로 서브되는
one large network but they cannot share primaries in a good way so you
하나의 큰 네트워크는하지만, 그들은 당신이 그렇게 좋은 방식으로 예비 선거를 공유 할 수 없습니다
understand this you have to notice the following if we do it for us and we
이것을 이해하면 우리는 우리와 우리를 위해 그것을 할 경우 다음 사항을주의해야
randomly drop off some of the units than in backward pass think about what
무작위로 무엇을 생각 뒤로 패스에 비해 단위의 일부를 내려
happens with the gradient right so I suppose we bring a random dropped off
나는 우리가 임의의이 내려 가지고 가정 오른쪽도록 그라데이션 발생
these units in a backward pass we're back propagating through the max that
후방 패스에서 이러한 단위는 우리가 다시 최대를 통해 전파하고 그
were induced by the dropout so in particular only the neurons that were
했다 특히 만 뉴런의 수 있도록 드롭 아웃에 의해 유도 된
used in a forward pass will actually be updated or have any grievance flowing
전진 패스에 사용 실제로 업데이트 또는 불만이 흐르는이됩니다
through them because any neuron that was shut off 20 no gradient will flow
차단 된 모든 신경 세포가 20 아니 그라디언트 흐름 없기 때문에 그들을 통해
through it and its weights to its previous layer will not be updated so
그것과 이전 계층의 무게를 너무 업데이트되지 않습니다
actively anymore on that was dropped out its connections to the previous layer
적극적으로 더 이상 그에 이전 계층으로의 연결을 중퇴했다
will not be updated and it was just it's as if it wasn't there so really what the
업데이트 그냥했다 그렇게 정말 무엇을이없는 것처럼 그건되지 않습니다
drop-off masks your sub sampling a part of your neural network and you're only
당신의 신경 네트워크의 일부를 샘플링 마스크 하위 오프 삭제하고 만있어
training that neural network on that single example that you happen that
교육 당신이 일이 발생할 것이 그 하나의 예에 신경 네트워크
point in time so as one model and gets rained on only one data point
시간의 점은 하나의 모델은 하나의 데이터 포인트에 비가 가져옵니다 있도록
ok I can try to repeat that
확인을 나는 것을 반복 시도 할 수 있습니다
came from somewhere here I want you guys to understand this or not
여기 어딘가에에서 온 너희들이 아닌지를 이해하려면
ok so when you drop drop drop in your own I wish I had the example of the
당신이 당신의 자신의 드롭 드롭을 삭제할 때 확인 그래서 내가이의 예 있었으면 좋겠다
neuron right but if I drop in the value I multiply its up to buy 09 its effect
내가 곱 값에 드롭하면 신경 세포의 오른쪽하지만 최대 09 그 효과를 구입
on the loss function there's no effect right so its gradient 10 because it's
손실의 기능에 영향은 경사 (10)가 있기 때문에 바로 그래서이 없다
about he was not used in computing the loss and so it's weights will not get an
그는 손실을 계산에 사용하고 그래서 안되었다에 대한 가중치는을받지 않습니다
update and so it's as if we've subsample a part of the network and we only train
업데이트 우리는 네트워크의 일부를 표본했는데 것처럼 그래서 우리의 단지 열차
that single data point that currently came to network with only trained on it
현재 만에 훈련과 네트워크 나니 하나의 데이터 포인트
and every time we do it for possibly subsample two different part of your
모든 시간 우리의 가능성 표본이 다른 부분을 위해 그것을 할 당신의
neural network but they all share parameters so it's kind of like a weird
신경망하지만 이상한 같은 종류의 그래서 그들은 모두 공유 매개 변수
ensemble of lots of different models all training Monday a point but they all
다른 모델의 많은 모든 교육의 앙상블 월요일이 점하지만 그들은 모두
share parameters so that's kind of roughly the idea here doesn't make sense
공유 매개 변수 즉 이해가되지 않습니다 여기 종류의 약 아이디어 그래서
usually save 50% is a very rough way to raise the same size so in this in this
일반적으로 50 %이이 그렇게 동일한 크기를 발생하는 매우 거친 방법 저장
world powers will notice we actually computer H
세계의 힘은 우리가 실제로 컴퓨터 H 알
we compute them just as we did before all of the computer it more than half of
우리는 우리가했던 것처럼 컴퓨터의 모든 전에를 계산하는 것이 더의 절반 이상
the values will get dropped 20
값은 20 떨어졌다 얻을 것이다
nothing changes they're good
아무것도 그들이 좋은거야 변경되지 않습니다
stations instead of competing on the issues you want to compete in the roads
대신 문제에 대한 경쟁 역은 도로에서 경쟁 할
are not being dropped in that case you want to do sports updates so you could
당신은 당신이 할 수 있도록 스포츠 업데이트를 수행 할 경우에 삭제되지 않습니다
in theory but I don't think that's unusual in practice we don't worry about
하지만 이론적으로 나는 실제로 우리가 걱정하지 않는 이상한 생각하지 않습니다
it too much and so you always gotta work training so every single iteration we
너무 많이하고 그래서 항상 돼 작업 훈련 그래서 매일 반복 우리를
get a minute match we sample or noise pattern for what we're gonna drop out
우리가 거​​ 드롭하는지에 대해 우리가 샘플 분 경기 또는 노이즈 패턴을 얻을
and go forward and backward pass and the gradient and we keep turning this over
앞으로 가고, 뒤로 패스와 그라데이션 우리는이 이상을 선회 계속
and over again so your question is like somehow cleverly true the binary mask in
또 다시 그래서 당신의 질문에 어떻게 든 영리 사실 바이너리 마스크처럼
like a way that best optimize the model or something that not really I don't
최고의 정말 안되지 않은 모델 또는 뭔가를 최적화하는 방법 등
think that's done or anyone has looked into too much sorry I yes I'm going to
이루어집니다 또는 누군가가 내가 그래 내가 갈거야 너무 미안 들여다했다고 생각
get into that in one slide next slide
하나의 슬라이드 다음 슬라이드에 해당 들어가
we're going to look at this time I'll take up one last question
우리는이 시점에서 볼거야 나는 마지막 질문을 할게요
questions one drop out to different amounts in different layers you can
질문 하나 다른 레이어에 다른 양에게 드롭을 수행 할 수 있습니다
there's nothing stopping you
당신을 중지 아무것도 없다
its intuitively you want to apply stronger drop out if you need more
그 직관적으로 당신은 당신이 더 필요하면 밖으로 강한 드롭을 적용 할
regularization so there's a layer that has a huge amount of Primaris will see
정규화 그렇게 볼 수 Primaris의 엄청난 금액을 갖는 층 거기
that income that's in one example you want to hit by strong drop out there
하나의 예에있어 소득 당신은 거기에 강한 하락에 의해 명중 할
conversely there might be some layers that we'll see what the network's early
반대로 우리가 어떤 네트워크의 초기에 볼 수 있습니다 몇 가지 레이어가있을 수 있습니다
on the comedy show layers are very small he don't really play as much drop out
코미디 쇼 층은 그가 정말 많은 드롭을 연주하지 않는 매우 작은
there it's quite common for example the color networking going to this in a bit
거기에 조금이가는 컬러 네트워킹은 예를 들어 아주 흔한 일
you start off with a low dropout ending up over time so the answer to that is
당신은 그 대답은 그래서 낮은 드롭 아웃 시간이 지남에 끝나는로 시작
yes and I forgot your second question can you instead units dropout just
예 내가 두 번째 질문은 당신이 대신 단위 그냥 드롭 아웃 할 수 잊었다
individual weights you can and that's something called dropped connect we want
당신이 할 수 있고 그 뭔가라고 각각의 가중치는 우리가 원하는 연결 삭제
to go into too much in this class but there's a way to do that as well i got
이 클래스에서 너무 많이 들어가 있지만,뿐만 아니라 내가 가진 것을 할 수있는 방법이있다합니다
now it s time i trust ideally what you want to do is we've introduced all this
지금은 내가 당신을 우리는이 모든 것을 도입했습니다되어 수행 할 작업을 이상적으로 신뢰하는 시간이야
noise right into the park pass and so if you would like to do now it just time as
바로 공원으로 노이즈가 통과하고 그래서 당신은 단지 시간과 지금 좋아하면
we'd like to integrate out all that noise and want to cuddle approximation
우리는 모든 소음을 통합하고 근사를 좋아 하죠하려는 싶습니다
to that would be something like you have a test image that you like to classify
그 뭔가를 것에 당신은 당신이 분류하려면 테스트 이미지를 가지고있는 것처럼
you can do many forward passes with many different settings of your binary masks
당신이 할 수있는 많은 전진은 바이너리 마스크의 다양한 설정으로 전달
and you're only using the subnetworks and then you can averaged across all
당신은 단지 서브 네트워크를 사용하고 모든 걸쳐 평균 수
those probably distributions so that would be great but unfortunately is not
그래서 그 아마 배포판은 중대하지만 불행히도 아닌 것
very efficient so it turns out that you can actually approximate this process to
매우 효율적 그래서 당신이 실제로이 과정을 근사 할 수 있습니다 밝혀
some degree has given to point out when first introduced dropout and the way
첫 번째 드롭 아웃과 방법을 도입 할 때 어느 정도는 지적 주신
will do this intuitively you want to take advantage of all your neurons you
당신이 당신의 신경 세포 모두 당신을 활용하고자 직관적으로이 작업을 수행합니다
don't want to be dropping my random we're going to try to copy the way we
내 무작위 우리가 길을 복사하려고거야 떨어지고 싶지 않아 우리
can leave all the neurons turned on so dunno drop out in a forward pass on a
몰라 A의 전진 패스에서 드롭 그래서 온 모든 신경을 남길 수 있습니다
test image but we have to actually be careful with how we do this so we can so
테스트 이미지 그러나 우리는 실제로 우리가 이것을 어떻게 우리가 그렇게 할 수 조심해야
in a poor pass your test images we're not going to drop any units but we have
가난한 우리가 어떤 단위를 드롭하지 않을거야 테스트 이미지를 전달하지만 우리는이
to be careful with something and basically one way to get that what the
얻을 것을 기본적으로 하나의 방법에주의하는 그 무엇
issue is supposed that this was an Iran and its got two inputs and I suppose
문제는 이것이이란과의있어 두 개의 입력이었다고 생각 나는 생각한다
that with all these inputs present at this time so we're not dropping unit so
이 시간에 존재하는 모든 입력을 그래서 우리는 그렇게 단위를 포기하지 않을 것을
it s time these two have some activations and the other doctors near a
이들 두 사람은 가까운 일부 활성화 및 다른 의사가 시간이야
computer to be some value tax yet to compare this
컴퓨터는이 비교 아직 어떤 값 세금이 될 수 있습니다
value of x two what the neurons out but would be during training time in
훈련 시간 동안 것 뉴런 밖으로 무엇을하지만 X이 값
expectation ok because in training time this dropout masks very randomly and so
이 때문에 드롭 아웃 마스크 매우 무작위 등 교육 시간에 확인 기대
there are many different cases that could have happened any different in
어떤 다른 일어날 수있는 여러 가지 경우가있다
those cases of this would be a different scale and have to worry about this let
이들 경우 다른 규모가 될이하자에 대해 걱정해야 할 것
me show you exactly what this means I think this
날이 내가이 생각을 의미 정확히 무엇을 보여
computes say there's no nonlinearity were only looking at the lingering Iran
더 비선형 만 남아있는이란에가보고되지 않았다이야 말할 계산해서
during stress tests this activation becomes W 0 which is the wait here 10
스트레스 테스트 중에이 활성화되는 (가) 여기에 10 대기 0 W된다
sacks + W one times why oK so that's what I want to compute a test on and the
자루 + 한 번 W 이유를 확인 그것이 내가에 테스트를 계산하기 위해 원하고 무엇 때문에
reason I have to be careful is that during training time the expected output
내가 조심해야 이유는 교육 시간 예상 출력 중입니다
of a in this particular case would have been quite different so we have four
이 특정한 경우에 아주 달라졌을 것의 우리는 네가
possibilities we could drop one or the other or both or none so in those four
우리는 그 4에 하나 또는 다른 또는 둘 모두 또는 없음을, 그래서 드롭 수있는 가능성
possibilities
가능성
computer different Valley was actually crunch do this math you'll see that when
컴퓨터에 다른 계곡은 실제로 당신이 때를 볼 수 있습니다이 수학을 위기했다
you reduce it
당신은 그것을 감소
you end up with one half off WRX + W one times why so in expectation at training
당신은 왜 그렇게 훈련에서 기대에 WRX + W 하나 끄기 시간을 절반으로 끝낼
time the update of this neuron was actually just time and so when you want
시간이 신경 세포의 갱신은 실제로 단지 시간이었고, 그래서 당신은 할 때
to use all the time you have to compensate for this and this and that
이것과 이것 저것을 보상하기 위해 당신이 가진 모든 시간을 사용하는
happened away as coming from the fact that we've dropped units with probably
우리는 아마와 단위를 삭제 한 사실에서 오는 멀리 일
the half and so that's why this end up being half and so with probably point
이를 최대 절반 그래서 아마 포인트 인 이유 절반은 그래서이다
five Olympic Singapore pass so basically if we did not do this then we end up
다섯 올림픽 싱가포르는 우리가 결국 다음 그래서 기본적으로 우리는이 작업을 수행하지 않은 경우 통과
having to large enough but compared to what we had an expectation during
우리는 동안 기대 한 것에 비해 충분히 크지 만에 갖는
training time and you're out the distribution will change and basically
분포가 기본적으로 변경됩니다에서 교육 시간과 당신이있어
things in the world that would break because they're not used to seeing such
그들은 이러한보고에 사용하지이기 때문에 휴식 것이 세계의 것
large epithermal neutrons and she have to compensate for that and you have to
큰 고온 열 중성자 그리고 그녀는 그 보상해야하고 그럴 필요
squish down so you're not using all your things instead of just happened things
그냥 일을 일의 대신 모든 물건을 사용하지 않도록 아래로 뭉개 버려
but you have to scratch daily activations to get back to recover your
하지만 당신은 복구를 다시 얻기 위해 매일 활성화에 스크래치가 당신의
expected output ok this is actually a tricky point but I think I was told once
예상 출력 확인이 실제로 어려운 점이지만 내가 한 번 들었다 생각
a story that when Jeff Hinton came up with drop out in the beginning he
제프 힌튼은 처음에 밖으로 드롭 함께 왔을 때 이야기하는 것이 그
actually didn't fully come up with this part so we tried drop out any didn't
어떤하지 않았다 밖으로 우리가 드롭을 시도 그래서 실제로 완벽하게이 부분을 마련하지 않았다
work and actually the reason it didn't work as he he missed out on this tricky
일을하고 실제로 이유는 그가이 까다로운 놓쳤다 그가대로 작동하지 않았다
point actually admittedly and so we have to scale your activation
실제로 인정 하듯이 지적 그래서 우리는 당신의 활성화를 확장해야
system down because of this effect and then everything works much better so I
아래 때문에이 효과의 시스템 다음 모든 것이 훨씬 더 그렇게 작동 I
just I'm just to show you what this looks like we basically compute these
그냥 우리가 기본적으로 이러한 계산처럼이는 모습을 보여 그냥 해요
neural nets as normal so we can be the first or second but now it just time we
정상적으로 신경망은 그래서 우리는 첫 번째 또는 두 번째하지만 지금은 그냥 시간이 우리가 될 수 있습니다
have to multiply by P so for example of peace haha dropping probability scale
평화의 예를 들어 하하 확률 규모를 삭제하도록 P를 곱해야
and down the activation so that the expectation expected out but now has the
되도록 활성화 아래로 기대 밖으로 예상하지만 지금은이
same as expected output in the training time and so at this time you actually
이 때 실제로 당신의 교육 시간 등의 예상 출력과 동일
recover for dropout and expected outputs are matching and this actually works
드롭 아웃에 대한 복구 및 예상 출력이 일치하고이 실제로 작동
really well so I'm dropping from this is just the discrepancy between train and
정말 잘 나는이에서 떨어지는거야, 그래서 기차와 사이에 단지 차이입니다
test like every using all your neurons are dropping them there's a discrepancy
모든 신경 세포를 사용하여 모든 같은 테스트를 불일치가있어 떨어집니다
so either you can correct it at this time or you can use what we call in
그래서 어느 당신은이 시점에서이를 수정하거나 우리가 부르는 당신은 사용할 수 있습니다
Burley dropout which I'll show you in a bit so we'll get to that in a bit
내가 조금 당신을 보여주지 벌리 드롭 아웃은 그래서 우리는 비트에 그에게거야
dropout summary if you want to drop out drop your units with probably off with
드롭 아웃 요약 당신은 아마 해제와 함께 드롭 당신의 단위를 삭제하려면
keeping a probability of pee and then it just forget to scale them so if you do
오줌의 확률을 유지하고 그것은 단지 당신이 경우에 그렇게를 확장하는 것을 잊지
this network will do will work better
이 네트워크는 잘 작동 할 것
ok and don't forget to also back propagate the masks which I'm not
확인도 다시 아니에요 마스크를 전파하는 것을 잊지 마세요
showing an inverted dropout by the way to do is to take care of this
할 수있는 방법으로 반전 드롭 아웃을 보여주는 것은이 알아서하는 것입니다
discrepancy between the train and test solution a slightly different way in
기차 및 시험 용액 약간 다른 방식 간의 불일치
particular what we'll do is we're changing this year so before you one was
당신 일이었다 전에, 그래서 특히 우리가 할 거 야하는 것은 우리는 올해를 변경하고
a biomass cups frozen ones we're not going to do is we're going to do the
우리가하지 않을거야 바이오 매스 컵 냉동 것들은 우리가 할 거 야한다
scaling here at training time so we're going to scale down the activations a
우리가 정품 인증 a를 아래로 확장 할거야, 그래서 교육 시간에 여기에 확장
trying time for another skill them up because if he spent five then we're
그는 다섯은 우리가있어 소비 때문에 경우 다른 스킬을 시간을 노력
boosting accusations a train time by hot and then it s time we can leave our code
비난에게 뜨거운하여 기차 시간을 강화하고 우리가 우리의 코드를 떠날 수있는 시간이야
touched right so we're doing the boosting of the activations a train time
바로 그래서 우리는 기차 시간 활성화의 증폭을하고있는 만진
we're making everything artificially greater by two acts and then it s time
우리는이 행위에 의해 인위적으로 더 큰 모든 것을 만들고있어 후 시간이야
we're supposed to have but now we're just going to recover the clean
우리는이 거 야하지만 지금 우리는 단지 청소를 복구하는거야
expressions because we've done the scaling a trying time so now you'll be
우리가 지금 스케일링하려고 시간을 수행 한 표현 때문에 당신은 수 있습니다
you'll be properly calibrated expectations between the train and test
당신은 제대로 기차와 시험 사이의 기대를 보정 할 수 있습니다
every year on and work that's right so using a dropout that's most common want
가장 많이 찾는이의 모든에 년과 오른쪽 그래서 드롭 아웃을 사용하고 작업
to use in practice so infected really comes down to a few lines and then the
그래서 정말 감염 실제로 사용하는 것은 다음 몇 줄과 아래로 온다
backward pass changes a bit but the networks almost always work better with
뒤로 패스 조금 변경하지만 네트워크는 거의 항상 함께 잘 작동
this unless you're severely under fitting in their actual exact and that's
이 당신은 실제 정확한에 피팅에서 심각 아니라면 그이다
why this is as i mentioned here
내가 여기에 언급 한 이유는
approximation is an approximation to assemble and one of the reasons an
근사는 조립 근사하고 이유 중 하나 인
approximation is because once you actually happened in the picture then
실제로 다음 사진에서 일어난 일단 때문에 근사값입니다
these expected outputs are all kind of screwed up because of the nonlinear
이러한 예상 출력은 모든 종류의 때문에 비선형의 망쳐된다
effects on top of these questions thank you for pointing that I go ahead
이러한 질문의 상단에 효과 내가 가서 것을 가리키는 주셔서 감사합니다
I see you're saying that they are inverted drop-in and drop-out are not
내가없는 당신은 그들이 드롭 인 (drop-in)과 드롭 아웃 반전 말을하는지 참조
equivalent so doing her job whether or not is not a problem because of the the
동등한 그렇게 여부 때문에 상기의 문제가 아니다 그녀의 일을하고
nineties I'd have to think about it maybe maybe you're right you may be
내가 가진 것 구십 어쩌면 당신이 바로 당신이 될 수있는 아마 그것에 대해 생각합니다
right here and I think all of this is just about expectations in expectation
여기 나는이 모든 단지 기대에 기대에 대한 생각
you're dropping a half and so that's the correct thing to use even though there's
당신은 절반을 삭제하고 있고 그래서 거기에 불구하고도 사용할 올바른 일이
some randomness in exactly the amount that actually end up being dropped
실제로 결국 정확히 양에 약간의 임의성이 삭제되고
okay great
큰 괜찮아
oh yeah there's like to tell you as a fun story will drop out so I was in a
이 오, 그래의 그래서이 있었다 밖으로 떨어질 것이다 재미있는 이야기로 당신에게 좋아
deep learning summer school in 2012 and Jeff Hinton was for the first time or at
2012 년 제프 힌튼에 깊은 학습 여름 학교는 처음으로 나 있었다
least the first time I saw it
적어도 처음 봤어
presenting dropout and so he's basically just saying okay said your neurons 20 at
드롭 아웃을 제시하고 그래서 그는 기본적으로 그냥 괜찮 말하는 것을 당신의 뉴런 (20)에서
random and just I'm just busy activations and this always works better
랜덤 그냥 난 그냥 바쁜 활성화를 해요이 항상 잘 작동
better and we're like wow that's interesting as a friend of mine sitting
더 나은 우리는 내 친구가 앉아으로 그 흥미로운 와우 같은거야
next to me he just pulled up his laptop right there he has a station has
내 옆에 그는 단지 바로 그 역이 있음 자신의 노트북을 뽑아
University machines and implement it right there during the talk and by the
대학 기계와 이야기하는 동안과가 바로 그것을 구현
time Jeff Hinton finish to talk he was getting better results and getting
시간 제프 힌튼 마무리는 그가 더 나은 결과를 얻고지고 있다고 얘기
actually state of the art reporter like
실제로 미술 기자의 상태 등
on his data that he was working with the fastest I've seen someone go like get an
그는 빠른 작업 한 자신의 데이터에 나는 누군가가 내려면 같이 가서 봤어요
extra 5% it was right there and then while Japan too much going to talk I
일본은 너무 많이 나는 이야기를하려고하면서 추가로 5 %가 바로 다음이었다
thought that was really funny there's very few times actually the something
즉, 무언가가 실제로 매우 몇 번 거기에 정말 재미라고 생각했다
like this happens it's a dropout is a great thing because it's one of those
이런처럼 그것이 그 중 하나이기 때문에 드롭 아웃은 훌륭한 일이다
few investors that is very simple and it always works just better and there's
소수의 투자자는 매우 간단하고 항상 그냥 잘 작동하고있다
very few of those kinds of tips and tricks that we've picked up and I guess
내가 생각 우리가 주운 팁과 트릭의 이러한 종류의 거의
the question is how many more simple things like dropout are there and that
문제는 얼마나 더 많은 간단한 일 드롭 아웃 등을들 수있다 거기입니다
just give you two percent boost
당신에게 2 %의 활력을 불어
always so we don't know
항상 우리는 모른다
ok so I was going to go on at this point into gradient checking but I think I
확인은 그래서 그라데이션 검사로이 시점에서 갈 거라고하지만 난을 생각한다
actually I decided I'm gonna skip this because I'm tired of all the neural
실제로 나는 모든 신경의 피곤 때문에이 작업을 건너 내가거야 결정
network like we've been talking about lots of details in training all that
우리와 같은 네트워크는 모든 훈련의 세부 정보를 많이 얘기했습니다 그
works and I think you guys are tired as well and so I'm going to skip gradient
작품과 내가 너희들뿐만 아니라 피곤하고 그래서 그라데이션을 건너 뛸 것 같네요
checking because it's quite well described herein notes I encourage you
그것은 아주 잘 노트 여기에 설명되어 있기 때문에 체크 나는 보시기 바랍니다
to go through it is kind of a tricky process takes a bit of time to to
그것은 까다로운 과정의 종류를 통해 이동하는 시간의 비트에 소요
appreciate all the difficulties with the process and so just read through it I
프로세스의 모든 어려움을 감사하고 그래서 그냥 내가 읽어
don't think there's anything I can drive around to make it more interesting to
에 더 흥미 수 있도록 내가 주위에 드라이브 수있는 일이 생각하지 않습니다
you so I would encourage you to just check it out
당신은 그래서 난 그냥 그것을 확인하는 것이 좋습니다 것
meanwhile we're going to jump right hand and it's going to come that works and
한편 우리는 오른손을 뛰어거야하고 ​​그 작동 올 것와
look at pictures so look like this this is Aileen at five from nineteen eighty
사진을보고 너무 1980년에서이 다섯에서 아일린입니다 같이
roughly and we're going to go into details of how commercial networks mark
대략 우리는 어떻게 상용 네트워크 마크의 세부 사항에 갈거야
and in this class we're not actually going to do any of the low-level details
이 클래스에서 우리는 실제로 낮은 수준의 세부 사항을 수행하지 않을거야
I'm just going to try to give you intuition about how this field can about
내가 얼마나이 분야에 대한 수에 대한 당신의 직관을 제공하기 위해 노력하겠습니다
some days total context and just come back from that works in general so if
어떤 일 전체 상황과 그냥 그에서 오는 일반적으로 작동 그렇다면
you'd like to talk about the history of commercial networks you have to go back
당신은 당신이 돌아 가야 상업 네트워크의 역사에 대해 이야기하고 싶습니다
to roughly nineteen sixties experiments approval and weasel so in particular
특히 이렇게 대략 아홉 육십 실험 승인 및 족제비에
they were studying the primary visual cortex and cat and they were sending an
그들은 차 시각 피질 고양이를 공부하고, 그들은은을 전송했다
early visual area and the cat brain as the cat was looking at patterns on the
초기 시각 영역과 고양이와 고양이의 뇌는에 패턴을 찾고 있었다
screen and they ended up actually winning a Nobel Prize for this sometime
그들은 끝내었고, 화면은 실제로이 언젠가 노벨상을 수상
later for these experiments as we'd like to show you what these experiments look
이후이 실험을 위해 우리는이 실험이 보는 무엇을 게재 할로
like just so they're really fun to look at so I pulled up eighty video here in
그냥 그렇게처럼 그들은 내가 여기 여든 비디오를 뽑아 그렇게 보면 정말 재미있어
and see what's going on here is the cat is fixed in position and we're recording
여기에 무슨 고양이가 위치에 고정되고, 우리가 기록을하는지 참조
from its cortex somewhere in the area of processing which is in the back of your
뒷면에 처리 영역의 어딘가의 피질에서
brain could be one and now we're showing different light patterns to the cat and
뇌가 하나가 될 수 있고, 지금 우리가 고양이에 다른 빛의 패턴을 표시하고 있고
we're recording and sharing the neurons fire for different stimuli let's look at
우리는 이제 살펴 보자 기록과 다른 자극에 대한 신경 세포의 불을 공유하고
how this experience will look like
어떻게 경험과 같이 표시됩니다
here
이리
experiments like these cells and they seem to turn all four edges in a
이러한 세포와​​ 같은 실험 그들은 모두 네 모서리를 설정하는 것
particular orientation and they get excited about the edges and one
특정 방향 그리고 그들은 가장자리와 일에 대한 흥분
orientation and northern orientation does not excite them and so like this
방향과 북쪽 방향은 다음과 같이 그래서 그들을 자극하지 않습니다
through a long process like a 10 minute video so we're not going to do this for
10 분 비디오와 같은 긴 과정을 통해 우리는이 작업을 수행하지 않을거야
a long time they spirited and they came up with a model of how the visual cortex
오랜 시간 그들은 분방하고 어떻게 시각 피질의 모델로 등장
process information in the brain and so they can several things that ended up
공정 뇌의 정보 및 그래서 그들은 몇 가지 결국 수 있습니다
leading to the Nobel Prize for example they figured out that the cortex is
예를 들어 노벨상을 선도 그들은 피질가 있음을 알아 냈다
arranged
배치
topically the visual cortex and what that means is that she was my printer
국소 적 시각 피질 어떤 것을 의미하는 것은 그녀가 내 프린터라고이다
basically nearby cells in the cortex so this is cortical tissue unfolded nearby
피질에서 기본적으로 근처의 세포 그래서이있다 대뇌 피질의 조직 인근 전개
salt air cortex are actually processing nearby areas in your visual field so
소금 공기 피질은 실제로 그래서 당신의 시야 인근 지역을 처리하는
you're whatever is not a recognized processed nearby and your bring this
당신은 인근 처리 인식되지 않는 및이를 가지고 어떤 것
locality is preserved in your processing and they also figured out that there was
지역은 당신의 처리에 보존되고 그들도 있다는 것을 알아 냈
an entire year of these roles what's called the simple cells and they
간단한 세포와​​ 그들이라고 무슨 이러한 역할의 전체 년
responded to a particular orientation of an edge and then there were all these
가장자리의 특정 방향으로 반응하고 이러한 모든 있었다
other cells that had more complex responses so for example some cells
일부 셀 예를 들어 더 복잡한 응답 있도록했다 다른 세포
would be turning offer specific orientation but were slightly
제공하는 특정 방향을 선회하지만 약간 있었다 것
translation invariant so they don't care about the specific position of the edge
그들은 가장자리의 특정 위치에 대한 번역 불변 걱정하지 않도록
but they only cared about the orientation and so they hypothesize
하지만 그들은 단지 방향에 대해 걱정하고 그래서 그들은 가설
through all of these experiments that the visual cortex has this kind of
시각 피질은 이런 종류의이 실험의 모든 통해
hierarchical organization where you end up a simple sell their reading to other
당신이 다른 단순한 판매 그들의 독서를 종료 계층 적 조직
cells called complex cells and etc and these cells are built on top of each
복잡한 세포 등 이러한 세포라는 세포는 각각의 상단에 내장되어 있습니다
other and the simple songs in particular have these relatively local receptive
특히 다른과 간단한 노래는 수용이 상대적으로 지방이
fields and they were building up more and more complex kind of representations
필드 이들은 표현의 더 복잡한 유형을 구축했다
in the brain through successive layers of representation and so these are
그래서이는 연속적인 표현의 층과를 통해 뇌의
experienced a lot of course some people are trying to reproduce this in
어떤 사람들은이 재현하려고하는 과정을 많이 경험
computers and trying to model the visual cortex with code and so one of the first
컴퓨터는 상기 제 때문에 하나의 코드와 시각 피질 모델링하려는 및
examples of this was gonna drop from Fukushima and he basically ended up
이 예는 후쿠시마에서 거 드롭이었다 그는 기본적으로 결국
setting up
설정
architecture with these local receptive cells that basically look at a small
기본적으로 작은 보면이 지역의 수용 세포 구조
region of the impact and then he stepped up layers and layers of these and so he
충격의 영역은 그 층과이 층 그래서 그는을 강화
had these simple assault on the complex also simple solves complex also the
또한 상기 복잡한 간단한을 해결해 단지에 이러한 간단한 공격했다
sandwich of simple and complex also building up into iraqi now back then
단순 및 복합도 그때 지금 이라크에 구축의 샌드위치
though in nineteen eighties back propagation will still not really around
하지만에서 아홉 년대 다시 전파 정말 주위에 아직하지 않습니다
and so pushing my head and unsupervised learning procedure for training these
그래서 이러한 교육에 대한 내 머리와 자율 학습 절차를 추진
networks with like a clustering scheme but this is not back propagates at the
클러스터링 방식 등으로 네트워크 그러나 이것은 다시되지 않습니다에 전파
time but it had this idea of successive layers small cells building up on top of
시간 그러나 그것은 상단에 건물 연속 층 작은 세포의 이런 생각을했다
each other and then these experiments further and he kind of built on top of
서로 다음이 실험 또한 그는 가지 위에 구축
work and he kept the architectural layout but what he did was actually
일을하고 그는 건축 레이아웃을 유지하지만 그가했던 것은 사실이었다
trainees network the back propagation and so for example he trained different
연수생은 다시 전파 네트워크 그래서 예를 들어 그는 다른 훈련
classifiers four digits or letters and so on and so trained all of it
분류 등 등 네 자리 숫자 또는 문자와 그것의 모든 훈련
backdrop and they actually ended up using this in complex systems that read
배경 및 그들은 실제로 읽어 복잡한 시스템이를 사용하여 종료
to check the radar like digits from postal mail service and so on and so
등 등 우편 서비스의 숫자와 같은 레이더를 확인합니다
that's actually go back to quite a long time ago to nineteen nineties and
즉 실제로 아홉 구십에 전 꽤 오랜 시간으로 돌아가 그리고
someone who was using them back then but they were quite small ok and so in 2012
사람이 2012 년에 이렇게 다시 그들을 사용하지만 괜찮 아주 작은했고, 누가
is when the come to start to get quite a bit bigger so this was the paper from
는이 용지에서했을 정도로 꽤 큰 얻을 시작하는 올 때
that I keep referring to escape into they took all of that and it's not as a
나는 그들이 그 모든했다으로 탈출 참조 유지하고는 같은 아니에요
dataset that comes actually from our lab so it's a million images with thousand
이 천으로 만 이미지, 그래서 우리의 실험실에서 실제로 제공 데이터 세트
classes huge amount of data you take this model which is roughly 60 million
클래스는 대략 6 천만 인이 모델을 데이터의 엄청난 금액을
parameters and cold in Alex net based on the first name of Alex Kozinski these
알렉스 Kozinski 이들의 이름을 기준으로 알렉스 그물에서 매개 변수 차가운
networks were going to see that they have names so this is Alex Knapp is a
네트워크는이 알렉스 냅이있다 그래서 그들은 이름을 가지고 있는지 가고 있었다
region that has that Google at their several minutes so just like this one is
이 일이 그렇게처럼 자신의 몇 분에서 구글을 가지고 지역
a limit and so we give them names so this was Alex net and it was the one
한계는 그리고 우리는 그들에게이 알렉스의 순이었다 그래서 이름을 부여하고 그것은 하나
that actually outperformed by quite a bit on the other algorithms what's
이 실제로 무슨 일이있어 다른 알고리즘을 꽤하여보다 실적
interesting to note historically is the difference between Alex nothing 2012 and
역사적으로주의하는 것이 흥미 알렉스 아무것도 2012 년 사이의 차이
the limit in nineteen nineties there's basically very very little difference is
열 아홉 90 년대 한도는 기본적으로 아주 아주 약간의 차이가있다
when you look at these two different networks this one used I think signals
이러한 두 개의 서로 다른 네트워크에서 볼 때이 사람은 내가 신호를 생각 사​​용
or 10 H pennies probably and this one is real and it was bigger and deeper and
10 H의 아마 동전이 하나는 진짜하고 더 깊은이었고,
was training GPU and have more data
GPU를 훈련하고 더 많은 데이터를 가지고 있었다
and that's basically it that's the only like that's roughly the difference and
그리고 기본적입니다 그것은 단지 그 같은 대략의 차이이다있어 그와
so really what we've done is we've figured out better ways of course
그래서 정말 우리가했던 것은 우리는 물론 더 나은 방법을 알아 냈어요된다
initializing them and it works better with national army and rebels work much
를 초기화하고 국가 군대와 더 잘 작동과 반군이 많은 작업
better but other than that it was just killing up both the data and compute
그것보다 더 있지만, 다른는 모두 데이터와 계산을 살해했다
but for the most part the actor was quite similar and we've done a few more
하지만 대부분의 배우가 매우 유사했다 그리고 우리는 몇 가지 더 많은 일을했습니다
tricks like for example they used a big filters will see that we use a much
그들은 큰 필터를 사용하는 예를 들어 같은 트릭은 우리가 많이 사용하는 것을 볼 수
smaller filters we also now this is only a few tens of players we now have a
작은 필터 우리 또한 지금이 우리가 지금이 선수의 수십입니다
hundred and fifty later come that so we really just skill is up quite a bit in
백 오십이 나중에 와서는 그래서 우리는 정말 스킬에 꽤 최대입니다
some respects but otherwise the basic concept of how you process information
어떤면하지만, 그렇지 않으면 당신은 정보를 처리하는 방법의 기본 개념
is similar
유사하다
oK so that's are now basically everywhere so they can do all kinds of
확인을 그래서 그들은 모든 종류의 작업을 수행 할 수 있도록 기본적으로 모든 곳에서 지금이다
things like classify things of course they're very good at retrieval so if you
물론 분류 것 같은 것들을 그들은 검색에 아주 좋은 경우 그래서 당신
show them an image they can retrieve other images like it they can also do
그들은 그것과 같은 다른 이미지를 검색 할 수 있습니다 그들에게 이미지를 보여 그들도 할 수있다
detection so here and there detecting dogs or horses are people and so on
검출 그래서 여기 저기 개와 말 등등 사람들과 검출
this might be used for example in some German cars all have this in the next
이 일부 독일 차, 예를 들어 사용될 수있는 모든 다음이가
line they can also do some experimentation so every single pixel is
선 그들도 그렇게 하나 하나의 화소가 몇 가지 실험을 수행 할 수 있습니다
labeled for example the person or a road or tree or sky rebuilding segmentation
예를 들어 표시된 사람이나 분할을 재건 도로 나 나무 나 하늘
for their use in cars for example here's an Nvidia Tegra which is small embedded
예를 들어 자동차에서의 사용을 위해 여기에 포함 된 작은 엔비디아 테그 라이야
GPU we can run come that's one reason for example this might be useful in the
우리가 올 실행할 수 있습니다 GPU는 예를 들어 하나의 이유는 이것이 유용 할 수 있어요
car where you can identify all the you can be skewed perception of rounding
당신이 식별 할 수있는 자동차는 모든 당신은 라운딩의 왜곡 된 인식 될 수 있습니다
things around you
당신의 주위에 물건
comments are identifying faces probably if you some of your friends are tacked
친구의 당신 일부는 식은 경우 의견은 아마 얼굴을 식별하는
on Facebook automatically it's almost certainly I would guess at this point
페이스 북에 자동으로 내가이 시점에서 추측 것이 거의 확실입니다
that video classification on YouTube identify what's inside YouTube videos
YouTube에서 해당 동영상 분류 YouTube 동영상 안에 무엇을 식별
they're used in this is a project from Google that was very successful where
그들은이에 사용하는 매우 성공적 Google의 프로젝트입니다
basically Google was really interested in taking street view images and
기본적으로 구글이 스트리트 뷰 이미지를 복용에 정말 관심과
automatically reading outhouse numbers from them
자동에서 바깥 번호를 읽고
ok and turns out this is a perfect astrakhan that so they had lots of human
확인을 밝혀이 그래서 그들은 인간을 많이했다 완벽한 아스트라한입니다
labor is at eight huge amounts of data and then put a giant comment on it and
노동의 데이터 팔 엄청난 양에 있고, 다음에 거대한 코멘트를 넣어
it ended up working almost as well as a human and that's the thing that we'll
그것은 인간으로 거의 잘 작동 결국 그는 일이 우리가 거
see throughout that this stuff works really really well make an estimate
이 물건 정말 정말 잘 추정을 작동 전반에 걸쳐 참조
poses they can play computer games
그들은 컴퓨터 게임을 재생할 수 있습니다 포즈
they detect all kinds of cancer or something like that and bye bye bye
그들은 그렇게 암 또는 무언가의 모든 종류를 감지하고 안녕히 가세요
images they can read Chinese characters recognized street signs this is I think
이미지는이 내가 생각입니다 거리 표지판을 인식 한자를 읽을 수 있습니다
segmentation of neural tissue they can also do things that are not visual so
신경 조직의 분할은 또한 이렇게 시각적없는 일을 할 수있다
for example they can recognize speech for speech processing they've been used
예를 들어, 그들이 사용했던 음성 처리를위한 음성을 인식 할 수있다
also for text documents so you can see that text into comments as well they've
또한 텍스트 문서에 대해 당신은뿐만 아니라 그들이했습니다 코멘트로 텍스트를 볼 수 있도록
been used for to recognize different types of galaxies they've been used to
이들이 사용되어 한 은하의 종류를 인식하기 위해 사용 된
in the recent cattle competition to recognize different Wales this is a
다른 웨일즈 인식하는 최근의 가축 대회에서 이것은이다
particular well there was like a hundred miles or something like that and that's
특히 잘 거기 백마일 같았다 또는 같은 그이다
just my specific individual so this will buy the pattern of its white spots on
그냥 내 특정 개인 그래서이 자사의 하얀 반점의 패턴을 살 것이다
its head is a particular way I'll become it has recognized so it's amazing that
머리는 그 놀라운 그래서 나는이 인식 될 수 있습니다 특정 방법입니다
works at all they're using satellite images quite a bit because now there are
모든 그들이 사용하는 위성 사진에서 작동 꽤 지금이 있기 때문에
several companies that have lots of satellite data so this is all analyzed
이 모든 분석 있도록 위성 많은 데이터를 가지고 여러 회사
with large comments in this case it's winding roads but you can also look at
이 경우 큰 의견으로는 도로를 권선 있어요 그러나 당신은 또한 볼 수 있습니다
agriculture applications or someone they can also do image capturing you might
농업 응용 프로그램 또는 그들은 또한 이미지를 할 수있는 사람은 당신에게 수도 캡처
have seen some of these results my work included as well we take images and
내 작품이 포함 된 결과뿐만 아니라 우리가 이미지를 가지고의 일부를 보았다
captions that more sentences instead of just a single category and they can also
자막 대신 단일 카테고리의 더 문장이 그들은 수도 있습니다
be used for various artistic endeavors
다양한 예술적 노력 사용될
so this is something called deep dream and we're going to go into how this
그래서 이것은 무엇인가라는 깊은 꿈이며 우리는 어떻게 들어갈거야
works
공장
actually implementing your third assignment may be ok maybe you will
실제로 세 번째 과제를 구현하는 것은 어쩌면 당신은 것입니다 확인 할 수있다
implement in your third assignment you give it an image and using that you can
세 번째 과제를 구현하는 당신은 그것을 이미지를 제공하고 사용 할 수있는 그
make it do weird stuff
이 이상한 물건을 할 수 있도록
particularly a lot of hallucinations of dogs and we're going to go into why dogs
특히 개 환각을 많이하고 우리는 왜 개에 갈거야
appear it has to do with the fact that image net which is where these networks
그것이 사실 여기서 이러한 네트워크하다 화상 순을 수행하는 표시
get trained to the end up they have a lot of dogs and so these these networks
최대 끝으로 훈련을받을 그들은 개 많은 등이 이러한 네트워크를
and apple juice and eating dogs it's kind of like they're used to some
사과 주스와 먹는 개는 그들이 일부를 사용하는의 같은 종류의
patterns and then you should have a different image you can make them put
패턴 및 당신은 다른 이미지를 당신이 그 (것)들을 넣을 수 있어야한다
them in the loop with the image and dole hallucinate things so we'll see how this
이미지와 루프에서 그들과 우리가 어떻게를 볼 수 있도록 환각 일을 나눠
works in a bit I'm not going to explain the slide but it looks cool so you can
나는 슬라이드를 설명하지 않을거야 비트에서 작동하지만 당신이 할 수 있도록 멋진 모습
imagine that it's probably involved somewhere I also want to point out that
내가 또한 지적 아마 어딘가에 포함 할 것 상상
what's interesting there's this paper called the networks rival representation
흥미로운 것은 네트워크 라이벌 표현 불리는이 종이있다
of private I think cortex call for a quarter of the recognition what they did
개인의 나는 그들이 무슨 짓을했는지 인식의 분기 피질 호출을 생각한다
here is basically looking at I think this was a macaque monkey and the
나는 이것이 원숭이 원숭이라고 생각하고 여기 기본적으로 찾고
recording from the ITV from the cortex here and there recording neural
여기 피질에서 ITV에서 기록과 신경이 기록
activations monkeys looking at images and then they fed the same images to
정품 인증 원숭이 이미지를보고 그들은 동일한 이미지를 공급
accomplish on your network and what they're trying to do is from the popular
네트워크에서 수행하는 것과 그들이하려는 것은 인기에서입니다
prom the commercial network code or from the population of neurons only sparse
상업 네트워크 코드 또는 전용 희소 뉴런 집단으로부터 무도회
population of context they're trying to perform classification of some concepts
문맥의 인구는 몇 가지 개념 분류를 수행하기 위해 노력하고
and what you see is that the coating from the idea cortex and classifying
무엇 당신이 보는 것은 그 아이디어 피질과 분류의 코팅
images is almost as good as using this neural network from 2013 in terms of the
이미지는 측면에서 2013이 신경 네트워크를 사용하는 것과 거의 같은 좋은
information that they're about the image you can do almost equal in performance
정보는 이미지에 대한 걸 당신은 성능이 거의 동일 할 수있다
for classification perhaps even more striking results here we're comparing
여기에 분류 아마 더 눈에 띄는 결과를 우리가 비교하는
the fed a lot of images through the competition at work and they got this
일의 경쟁을 통해 이미지를 많이 공급 그들은이있어
month he took a lot of images and then you look at how these images are
달 그는 이미지를 많이했다 다음은 이러한 이미지는 방법에 대해 알아
represented in the brain or in the comment
뇌 또는 의견 표현
so these are two spaces representation of how images are arranged in the space
그래서이 두 공간은 공간에 배치되는 방식의 이미지 표현이다
by the comment and you can compare the similarity matrices and statistics
주석에 의해 당신은 유사성 행렬 및 통계를 비교할 수 있습니다
you'll see that the I T cortex and the comment
당신이 볼 수 있다는 IT 피질과 코멘트
that's are basically very very similar representation there's a mapping between
의 매우 매우 유사 표현 기본적 것을 매핑 사이가있다
them it almost seems like similar things are being computed the way they arranged
비슷한 물건들이 배치 방법을 계산하고있다처럼 거의 보인다
a visual space of different concepts and what's closed and what's far is very
서로 다른 개념과 내용을 시각적으로 공간이 폐쇄 무엇을 훨씬 것은 매우가요
very remarkably similar to what you see in the in the brain and so some people
당신이 뇌에서에서 볼 무엇 때문에 어떤 사람들은 매우 매우 유사
think that this is just some evidence that companies are doing something brain
이 회사는 뭔가 뇌를하고 있다는 것을 그냥 몇 가지 증거가 있다고 생각
like and that's very interesting so the only question that remains then in that
같은 그것은 매우 흥미로운 점에서 다음 남아있는 유일한 문제 때문에
case
케이스
is this work
이 작품은
and we'll find out the next class
우리는 다음 수업을 찾을 수 있습니다